Music
Greetings! There we go!
Ha ha ha ha ha! What's going on, people?
Printing out a Pepsi. No! Not that! That's the worst!
I mean, uh, yes, it's the worst because I, I hate Pepsi, right? I, I love Coke Zero. Yes. Exactly.
Mm-hmm. So, I adjusted the audio of the music a little bit. I felt like it was a bit too loud last time.
The sound and the ambience are still at 100%. Hopefully it's going to be okay. So yeah.
Hey, what's up, Trevelyan Dova? Trevelyan Dova? Hi to you as well. How's the printing man, Oliver?
What printing man? I don't know nothing of such things. Wouldn't download a Pepsi, would you?
I remember that. That's a good one.
Anyway, uh, so I was definitely playing this game last time, right?
This is where I left off. I was playing, uh, Terraria. So, um, yeah, let's just get into this.
Yep, everything's going fine. Um,
I'm actually just gonna close you guys down here and jump straight into the game.
Um, let's see here. Oliver, that's my name. Uh, yep, 160 HP, 160 MP. Very nice.
Uh, hold on. Let me close you guys down.
Like that. Okay, I will see you guys on the other side. I hope you're gonna have fun.
Oh, I have to click this too. There we go. Okay, I have to remember how to do this now.
Uh, let's see here. I don't remember what I was doing.
Right, I need to get back into this, man.
Um, Oliver's body was mangled by a zombie. Yes, we've had many of such situations.
Um, Hano, my dear, what you're wearing is much too drab. You absolutely must take a lesson
in dying your tired attire. No, what about happiness? This place is quiet enough to
sleep like a sultan. Oh no, the forest does not inspire me. Don't like, don't like.
Um, I can agree with that. I also do not like the forest.
Um, right, I was doing things last time. I have this Abigail's flower.
This thing right here saved my ass. We had a demonic incursion happen
and I battled it off using flowers.
And that's about the last thing that happened, I believe.
Uh, we have a weather vane, which is nice and Ralph is here.
You want apples? Carrots? You want pineapples? We got torches.
Um, do you? You do? Huh, where's the pineapples?
You fucking liar.
A sickle. Hmm. Okay, okay. I gotta remember how to play this game.
Joe! Tell me how to play this game. They say there's a person... Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's you.
Um, crafting. I believe I was doing some crafting. I was looking up recipes and stuff.
Uh, can I use something with the bow? Can I? No, okay.
Can I upgrade this maybe? No? Or maybe there's some kind of recipe involving that?
Wait, am I not supposed to put things there? Okay, I am. Perfect. Oh!
I can make an iron skin potion using this.
Bottled water. How do I get that? I guess I start making a bottle and then I get some water.
Um, well, that's for another time. I said, oh wait, I wanted to go on an adventure.
That was my plan. So let's organize the inventory real quick.
This is the Michelinius chest, as it says here clearly. Ores and doors and organics.
Mm-hmm. I think it makes a lot of sense.
Ores and doors. We need to put in some tin ore and iron ore and all the others ores.
Why do we have such so many single ores here? It makes no sense to me.
Oh, I want to go fishing, too. Peddler's hat! I don't want that. I have a better one.
But maybe I can do something with it. Let's put it in here.
Clay block that counts to me is ore, even though it's not really ore. Let's put that in there
as well. I do want to bring the dirt block because I can use it to make bridges and stuff.
Shurikens. I want to try those for sure. Platforms are good to have when you're out exploring.
Archery potion. Sure. Breathe water instead of air. This seems pretty useful as well.
And then we have this one. This is a lesser healing potion. Hold on.
Maybe I can craft a bigger healing potion using a lesser one.
Hey, Joe! Can I make a big healing potion using this?
Yeah, I definitely can. I just need glowing mushroom! I have that!
I think. I remember glowing mushrooms. Definitely remember that.
Mushrooms. Organics. There it is. There it is. It's time to make potions.
Oh wait, I don't need to talk to you anymore. I know how to do it now.
I wonder if I have to be near this bench to do it.
Escape. Let's see. Potions. Mushroom table. Flaming mace.
Right, wasn't this worse? This one has 20. This one has 18.
But I guess it hasn't been randomized yet.
So I guess there is a chance it could be better if I do it.
That depends entirely on whether or not that actually does randomize every time you
change it. Man, where's this potion? Am I blind?
Potion. Potion. Potion. Joe? Joe, you weren't lying to me, were you? Be honest.
Let's see here. Glowing mushroom and lesser healing potion.
What's this? Decorative healing potion. Huh. That's kind of cool actually. This makes me
think there's many items in this game you can use to decorate with. You can probably decorate with
anything. Maybe I need like an alchemy station or something. Maybe the furnace.
Can I heat the potion in here or something? Okay, I don't know. Anyway, let's put it in here.
What is this music? Lens, glow sticks, chains, short get in there bowls.
This one I want to bring. This is nice. Tongsten bars goes in this one.
And let's see here. Mud block goes in also in here.
Zombie. This is definitely Michelinius. So is gel.
Amethyst. This has to be like ores related.
Bombs! These are cool. I need to use these a lot.
I need to have a good key bind for this. What should it be?
Hmm. Maybe this one. I can always use this to summon it, right? I just need to sort of click it.
So that's fine. The wall can also stay here.
And the wood as well. Nice. I think we're set to go on an adventure.
And you know what? Let's go to the desert. There's a desert to the east of here.
It needs to be explored.
So the question now is, can I just at any time?
Abigail's flower. Such a cute little flower there. Whoops.
There we go. Kind of forgot how to loot in this game. Let's go!
The sudden change. Oh.
Are you okay there? Give me that.
Interesting. Maybe it doesn't like the heat. Are you okay here? Abigail. What's this?
What's that? I can't pick it up, it seems. Wait, is that? Oh, that's sand. Okay.
What do we got here? Palm trees?
Oh, maybe I don't... I shouldn't do it like that. Okay. Dragonflies.
And probably use that in potion making. I need to use my thingy. Uh-oh. That's an enemy. Oh god.
Nice. Give me that. Also these trees, are they just gonna give me normal...
Wait, they're not palm trees. Obviously they're not gonna give me wood. What am I thinking?
I can't destroy this either. Oh, I need an axe of course. I'm an idiot. Hold on. Maybe I can destroy
these. I get it. I get it now. Take care of it. Oh god. I've been missing that sound.
What's that? Give me acorn and cactus. Palm wood.
This isn't... What if I... This is a test. I'm gonna plant a tree right here.
Wait, is it planted now? I'm gonna plant a tree right there and see if it grows a palm tree
or a normal tree. I guess it's gonna grow a palm tree since we're in the desert.
There we go. Taking care of... Also I need to eat. Oh, I didn't bring any food.
That's the issue right now. I have mushrooms. Nice. How am I gonna get across here?
I guess I use this, right? Oops. Oh no. That was terrible. Abigail, you didn't see that.
That was horrible. Oh, oh no. Oh no, what's this now again?
Reventuring into dangerous territory here, Abigail. It ain't good.
Ooh, there's a cave. Right or down. I'm gonna go down.
Cremera. Oh no. Hey, look at this. It's gonna take care of the enemies for me. I can just chill here.
Feels kind of broken, but sure. Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay. Let's be careful.
Oh, this is really dangerous. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no, I'm dying. I forgot how to heal.
There we go. Oh, shit.
I forgot how to combat. Everything's fine. Good thing I have a lot of HP now.
Fuck, yeah. Yeah, dude. Three recall potions. That's big. Arrows, I'll take it. Radar.
You're shitting me. How does that work? Grenade? Oh, I'm liking this.
Uh, why doesn't it... Oh, it's not stackable. Okay, I see. At least not with that. You can't
stack two different ones. I'm gonna take this chest with me. Also, I see oars.
Oh, give me tin. Dude, it's mining so quick. Holy shit. I kind of forgot I didn't have
this pickaxe last time. This was something I crafted at the very end. Uh, it's time for
platforming. Is this enough? Oh, not enough. That's okay. We don't have to have them like
perfectly aligned there. Okay, and torches. Oh, shit. Oh, no. Where's my weapon? Oh, I need
to be out of the menu. There we go. Nice. Good job, Abigail. Abigail is curing me right now.
And then...
God, I need to find a better way to do this. Did I use all my platforms? No, I didn't.
Okay, perfect. Give it a that. All right, fine. I guess we're dropping down. We're sort of...
Actually, fine. We have the potion of retrieval or reclamation or whatever you call it.
Resuscitation. No, I forget the name. Abigail is doing work here. Oh, God.
We're doing well so far, I want to say. Eat the mushroom.
Annoying cobwebs, get rid of that. Okay. Is this good for me?
Looks like some bloody water right there. I need to get up there.
Oh, I need to use the... Wait, how do I...
There we go. Oh! That's a trap!
Hold on, wasn't there... There was a key bind for something.
Quick heal. What does that actually do?
It just... I think it just auto-uses a potion you have.
I don't think it's going to eat. It's going to use a potion.
I'm going to use that button from now on. So there's traps here, huh?
Oh, yes, that's what I need. What do we have here? Is that good for me?
Is this water? Okay, is this also fine? This is some yellow water? Pisswasser.
Uh-oh, get up. Place one there. Dude, swimming is so difficult.
Okay. God, I feel like I forgot how to play this game. I was way more fluid last time.
At least you mine quick underwater, huh? Not like Minecraft, where it's pretty much impossible.
You got a red slime. We got a piece of me! Hey!
Come here. Wait, I'm not hitting shit.
I don't see anything interesting. Dude, you have a lot of breath.
You don't even need the potion for that.
I'm going to make a hole here and let the water flow through.
This is going to be glorious. Look at this. Look at that!
I love that. That's really nice.
You've got more tin. Beautiful. Very nice. Dude, I love the effect here with the water flowing.
What am I even doing down here? I'm just trying to go deep, I guess. What's that?
Oh, just a piece of something. Okay, buddy.
Okay. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Isn't this... is that it? Wait, what is this? Platinum! Yes, dude!
That's what I was looking for. Well, among other things.
Along with adventure, of course. Adventure in general. Yes, sir.
Give me that. Give me that.
Oh, this feels nice.
Okay. Is there anything else here?
Anything at all?
I don't think I should keep going down.
I feel like I should explore the cave as much as I can, you know? Oh, god.
The best way to get up. Do I have any of those things left?
Spider webbies? Nope. Crap.
Then do like this, and then we go up. We ascend. Oh, that's way better!
Look, you can just sort of put it right underneath you in the air. Also, what is that?
Holy shit, there's platinum here, too. Didn't even see that. Oh, god. Oh, god. This is a yellow slime.
Hey, buddy!
Man, no chance at all, huh?
What is that? There's something else here, too. Something purple.
Am I standing on one? I was. So we do like this.
What is that? Oh, that's the amethyst. Right. I found that last time, too. I remember now.
Go like that. And then here... Oh, perfect. Perfect. This was a nice little cave. I like this.
Do I see anything else here? That should be taken. What's that?
It was just a stone.
Crimson torch. What even is that? That looks kind of nice, actually. I do like that.
What's happening? Oh, fuck, that scared me. Yeah, I figured that was it. I remember something like that.
It's going to come here again now. Kill it. Nice. Also, what did it drop?
Silver. By the way, I need money. What if another wandering trader comes by, huh?
I need to be able to buy shit. How much money do I have? Nine gold, dude. That's actually pretty nice.
Come on. Jump higher, please. That's fine.
Okay. Perfect.
I send even more. Oh, wait, I could also go this way. Let's do that. I feel adventure in me.
Wait, that's crimson. Is this the glow one? This is a teal mushroom.
I used to make teal dye. That makes sense. Makes a lot of sense, actually.
Man, I really need one of those ropes. Can I make that here? What can I make?
Cactus workbench. Crimson campfire.
Yeah, I don't know, man. Nothing that piques my interest there. Let's go down first.
Is that a chandelier? Oh, fuck. Oh, no.
Oh, where's the button? Oh, no, I'm actually dying.
Oh, you're kidding me. God, I'm so terrible at this game. I dropped seven gold.
Okay, I need to go back immediately. All right. First death doesn't count.
Everyone knows that.
Okay, let's go back. I need that money right now. But before I go back,
let's quickly go up here to the chest and click on a certain button that is very special to me.
Look at that. That's fucking fantastic. I can't get enough of that button.
Sand block! We can probably make mirrors out of that cactus that is organic.
And the thing is, the more I fill up these chests,
the easier it's going to be to click on the button later that will autofill the chests, right?
That's freaking amazing. Spillunker potion! Shows the location of treasure and ore.
Speaking of, detects enemies around you. Oh, maybe I need to have the map open for that one.
That's very much possible. Hardened sand block. Sure, put it in.
Teal mushrooms go in here. We have wood also. I guess that's organic, you know. Waterleaf?
Sure. Another star. I should make the good arrows. Hold on. Do I have any...
I have two stars here. Oops. Let me grab some more.
How am I gonna... Oh shit, I can't get up there. Oh yeah, right, right, right. I could just collect
it through the thing. Perfect. Perfetto. Hey, oh my god. I wonder, does it do more damage
the more I swing it? That's like the question here. I like this song right here. This is a nice song.
Okay, let's go grab our shit and eat.
Joe, I'll be back later. We're gonna do some crafting. Mark my words.
The desert is no joke, but this time I'm prepared. I've gotten back into the game now.
Nice. Vulture. Oh, I need to...
Abigail! Nice. Now I remember why I have so much money. It's from the demonic incursion.
They dropped so much money. Wait, he dropped HP.
I haven't seen that before. He straight up just gave me HP when he died.
Antlion. Okay. Sure. Sure, sure. Stupid vultures. I'm not dead yet, you know.
What? Did Abigail just crit? What just happened?
Let's see. If I just click once and if I go like this...
There we go. Fuck you. Uh-oh, here we go again.
Let's survive the first onslaught here. Oh god. Jesus.
Okay. Wait, what's this? There's a bunch of money here.
Get it. Okay, take all that, go down here. Wait, is this where I went last time?
Oh wait, was my shit converted to the red? It's totally converting it.
This is some kind of a living thing, I think.
Uh, look at that pro shit right there. Did you see that? What's that?
Tin ore, right. Wait, did I actually go this way?
I guess I did. I just didn't put torches. I need to put torches so I don't forget where I was.
This is definitely where I was. And we have something here.
Oh yeah, I'm totally back in this game now. I will not die anymore today.
First death doesn't count, all that. It's gonna be easy from now.
And I need to figure out how to deactivate those traps. Maybe I can shoot it.
No. Where's the switch? Okay, so it's right there.
That's bad actually. What if I just remove this?
It's not shooting anymore.
Uh, man, it took a lot of my HP.
What have we got? Silver, yes. Uh, yep. Eight minutes?
I get the feeling potions are very important in this game.
Grab everything. Uh, that's great. I need that.
Bombs, band of regeneration.
No way. By the way, oh wait, I'm drawing. Can I zoom on this map?
Can I zoom in the game actually? Hold on.
Oh, what? What's happening? What just happened?
Uh, I can't heal. Hold on.
Yeah, I need to wait for this. Okay, hold on. Settings. Controls. Can I zoom?
Zoom in. Oem plus. Oh my god, I can.
Holy shit! I actually like it zoomed in a little bit. Let's go like that for now.
Let's see how this feels. Uh, we need to heal.
There we go. Let's see. Ah, this one is empty. Right, let me take this chest with me.
What's that? Oh yeah, tungsten chandelier!
Is there another button here? No, that was the button.
Oh, can I disable this shit?
Dart trap.
Loom. Dude, I can make my own traps.
That's kind of big.
Grab me all this. Awesome. Man, I feel like the game is a bit too loud for me.
Uh, actually I can just turn it down for... Actually, you know what? I'm going to ask
you guys right now. So, how is the game sound compared to my voice so far?
Because I can turn it down on my end, but not yours.
But if it's fine for you, I'm not going to change it.
Hold on, I'm just going to quickly alt tab out.
It's perfect. Okay, okay, nice. Thanks, guys. Looks like everybody says it's good.
That's awesome. Thanks.
I love the instant feedback you get from something like that. Okay.
Good to know. That reassures me. And now I can adjust the volume on my end
without affecting you. There it is.
Okay. Abigail, stop your whining.
It's time to... Oh, wait a minute. We've got stuff here. We've got stuff.
I love this. I got to say the water here is fantastic.
Get rid of that shit. The water is honestly... I'm really... I don't know why I'm so
impressed by that. That's... I haven't seen something like that
in a 2D game before.
Tungsten ore. That's also very nice to have.
Honestly, all... Oh, platinum! And we've got enemies. Abigail's got it. Thanks, dude.
Okay. Mind this. I wonder actually what the hammer is for.
So I figured out I can use it to remove walls, but then it's not very reliable and...
Wait. It actually works.
Wait. Like, it removes and then it places... It's like almost an adjustment tool or something.
Something that changes the state of something that is there.
That... Why can't I... Mind that?
Can I hammer that? Hey! I can hammer that!
That's the use. Look. Well, not quite. It's like... Whoa.
Okay. That's really weird. I don't understand this.
Also, we got something up there, but I don't care about that right now.
I'm gonna go down here and we're gonna use... We're gonna use the ultimate
survival kit. God damn it. Where is it? Where's my rope?
Oh, we're gonna have lots of problems with this stuff.
Oh, no shit. That's okay. There we go. Now we can get back up again.
I mean, dude, having that potion of relocation actually is amazing.
I don't really have to think too hard about going too far or getting too lost.
For one thing, I have a map, right? And then I can just instantly teleport back with everything.
That's kind of nuts.
I wonder if I can just use that mid-combat if I'm about to die.
Wouldn't be too shabby, huh? What is that? Oh, it's lead.
Man, it's so much quicker with this pickaxe. It feels amazing.
Nice. And then we have a place up here and some stuff down here. I'm gonna go down.
I'm feeling down right now.
Sure, just do that. What is that? Oh, it was a... wait a minute.
Activate the other thing. There we go.
Have I reached the bottom here of the world? I wonder.
But you can't really mine that red stuff.
Go further up.
Kind of looks like the end of the line here, doesn't it?
Dude, I'm getting a shit ton of tin and tungsten and all that shit.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
I feel like I've seen this sign before, by the way,
of this ghost. Call me crazy, but there's some kind of memory in me.
I mean, okay, ghosts kind of look similar in video games, right?
But there's just something about it. Give me all the tungsten.
I hear enemies, by the way. The big, bad ones. Nice. Okay, make a bridge.
Just to here. Just to see what we got. What is that?
Lead. Dude, it's really hard to tell these apart. Like, what is what? Platinum is easy.
But some of the other ones, I just need to get used to that.
What? Gimme that one. Yes. Ooh, we've got more here.
That's exciting. Why can't I mine this?
Notice how it changes shape when I... Look.
It's like reorganizing itself. It's not actually getting... Yeah, it's weird.
Oh, that works. Very interesting material there.
What is that? Sand? No! Wait, I died like this once before.
A rock fell on my face. I wonder if I had full HP or not just now.
God damn. Well, okay. Oh, I'm going back.
You know it. But first, we got to click on a very special button.
We click on the button, we high five Joe, we grab a snack, and then we...
Lay low. There. Look at that. Oh, I... I'm never gonna get old.
I'm gonna get tired of that. That's just amazing. Brown pressure plate?
Chandelier? Joe, you have been such a good guide for me. You deserve a goddamn chandelier.
That's right. Happiness for you. You're fond of wandering through the forest.
Well, be fond of the chandelier now that I gave you, okay?
Look at this cutie.
I really like when it's zoomed in a bit more here. This makes me happy.
Renée's planked wall. I feel like construction also should go into Michelinies.
Oh, you know what? Let's have this chest and call it...
Something else. Let's call it... construction.
You know, all kinds of things for like building the house and stuff.
Like that. And the loom I get. Oh, the loom. I think I know who wants a loom. Hano!
Look what I have for you. What can I do here with that?
Jester's... let me... okay, you know what? I'm gonna try this. Oh, you're right.
Oh yeah, look. Ruthless. 22 melee damage. Yes!
May the fire light your way. Minus 10% knockback. That's not good though.
But I guess... is this then a flaming fire damage, then? It says melee damage.
Not sure, actually.
Hano, do you have a... dive at?
One go... bro, the price is here. Can't believe it. What is wrong with these people?
I'm gonna take this because it's construction stuff.
Oh wait, this should have been called construction then, I guess.
Yeah, let's call this one construction instead. And the other one, Michelinius.
Construction. And then this one can be called Michelinius.
Very nice. Put this in here. Actually put it here for now.
Wait, I need to be able to get up. Can I still...? Oh yeah, fine. We're fine.
Michelinius. Construction is here, so this goes in. This goes in, this goes in.
Now, what is Michelinius here? Crimson block, and this is sort of Michelinius,
sort of that too, and that, and also this. The bowl. Detonator, guts and gory.
This is construction. Blue slime banner. Man, I wonder how to place the banners.
That is, ironically, one of the biggest mysteries in this game right now.
It's so weird. Why, that is such a big mystery.
Oh, this is organic. Put this in here. Gel, banners, bowls, pressure plates,
you know, all those weird ass items. The dart trap. I kind of want to put some at my base.
What the fuck is that? A goldfish. Oh, didn't give me anything.
Okay, that's too bad. Okay, water leaf seats. Go on organics.
Plate is here. Man, I need to try this. As soon as I get back, I'm trying it.
As soon as I'm getting the bunny. I guess that's an organic. It's put the bunnies in the box.
This is construction. What is happening here with these stars?
So many of them. Dirt wall. I'm going to take this wet rope with me. It's kind of useful.
Also the rope. Eat a little bit. Look at my little collection of animals and stuff.
This is food. Man, I need to go fishing. I'm excited about fishing.
But I haven't really found a good body of water yet.
With glow sticks. Let me take some of those.
And that seems good. Construction. Put this stuff in here.
Wood platform. Actually, yeah, sure. I take them with me. Okay, I think we're ready.
Let's grab some stars here. Hold on, can I?
Hey, there we go. Caught the goldfish. Oh, is that it?
Yes, it is. Oh, they come out while it's raining, of course. It makes sense.
Now I really want to go fishing. God damn.
Get in there. Oh, we can also sort. I forgot about that.
Sorting is great.
There's nothing else I should be doing, right? Joe. See you, Joe.
Okay. Oh, I see one enemy nearby. Oh, that's the sensor. I get it. I get it.
Give me all this. I'm hearing scary things. Let's deploy the one and only.
Man, this item is insane. Where did I even get that? That's the question right now.
I'm getting all the worms. It's planning for the future here.
Why did I go down over here? Look at this fucking zombie.
Is this doing... Oh, it's definitely putting it on fire.
Oh, yeah, this looks way cooler. I think I did the right thing operating that.
Wait, we got a body of water here. I know where to fish. Oh, god. Heal.
I really need a better key bind for that. H is not good.
It's way too much out of the way for the fingers.
There it is. But right now, all we need is to grab our money.
Did I go too far here? Hold on. I went too far, I think. Let me see the map.
Oh, no, I didn't. Okay, okay. Oh, oh, shit. Come here.
Man, is the range better on this now?
Oh, yeah. Oh, man, it's so much better when the game is zoomed in. I can actually see things. I was almost squinting before.
I like this. I can even zoom further in if I want. Look at that. Maybe that's a bit too much.
Maybe like that.
Give me that money. Abigail? No, no, no. Come with me. We have work to do.
Also, I need to use these bombs here. And I also have some grenades I want to try. So that's which one?
R, B. Let's try this.
Whoa! Yo, grenades rock. That's fantastic. Oh, god. Oh, god. It hit me. That bastard.
Okay, this is actually kind of insane. What's happening here?
Dude, I'm killing this. Eat this.
Another zombie. No chance against my flaming mace here. Spiders. That's okay.
Oh, god. It's jumping. Dude, this is how we farm money. Seven enemies nearby.
That's quite a lot. Okay, Abigail, let's go.
Where it goes, right? You can move through the ground. All right, see you later.
Come with me if you want to live. What's this? I think that is tin.
Yes. Yes, sir. Turn that off.
Nice. Okay, let's be careful of falling rocks.
What is this? Oh, what? I took some damage. I'm not sure what just happened.
I wonder if I can upgrade Abigail. Okay, we haven't been here. Where's my money?
Oh, no. I need that money. I wonder if I die now. Is that money lost,
similar to how souls are lost in Dark Souls? Or will they also ever stay there? That's the
question, right? I'm leaning towards the ladder option there. It's always going to stay.
Like, there's just going to be money scattered around everywhere.
Ah, look at that. We can actually see where we died.
It's almost unreal that there's a map in this game that helps me.
I'm not used to that lately. Okay, and I'll go this way.
Wait, what's that? Let's grab that real quick. Thank you.
Why didn't I put any torches down? I'm a silly goose.
There it is. We got the money. 11 gold now, baby. What is that? Can I hammer that?
Hold on, what does the hammer say?
50% hammer power. Annoying tungsten hammer.
Okay, well, I'm still not quite sure what that does.
Oh, I'm so scared of falling things.
Let's use the lesser one. I wonder if the automatic healing button is smart enough to only use lesser ones.
Is it the sand following on me here or what?
Oh, I think it is. Yeah, the sand falls on my head.
Ooh, that's scary, actually. Hardened sand.
Oh, there's something over there. It's another one of those cremeras, crime era.
Use this one. Nice. And rope, that's lovely. Give me all of this, too.
I actually don't know what my plan is right now. It's just exploring, I guess.
And look out for rocks falling.
Oh, here we go. Why is that not hitting? Oh, shit.
There we go. That was a bit weird.
Potion sickness. Anything on a fall on me? I can't go this way. There's too much red block.
Let's try this. See some stuff here to be mined.
I wonder what the objective is in this game, actually.
I mean, it's a survival game, right? So I guess the objective is to survive and thrive.
Similar to Minecraft. It's time for bombing.
Hey, people. I wonder if there's a way to make it explode after one second only, similar to worms.
Yo, this is a great way of digging. Yo, is that how I get through the red stuff?
I think I just realized something important. What do we got down there?
And you see, this is where I need to be able to zoom out as well.
Okay, Abigail is taking care of it. Any falling rocks?
So I'm gonna see if I can't get through this with the bomb. I have a shit ton of bombs.
Oh! Yay! Fuck yeah, dude!
Oh. Uh, let's go.
Uh-oh! Oh, I can just click anywhere and it will automatically make it longer.
That's a nice knowledge there. Also, I'm scared.
Bloodcrawler. Oh, I hate that. We gotta bomb these guys.
Awesome! So, I'm just gonna mine while Abigail takes care of these nasty enemies, huh?
That's smart. Topos!
Yeah! Give me all the gems.
What am I blowing up down there?
Don't throw it in there.
This is insane. I probably should get down there, huh?
Oh yeah, I can just hang out here.
That's a good strategy. Oh, I think we've got some crazy loot down here.
There's a heart! A beating heart there. You see that shit?
Oh, we got a lot of stuff. We need to eat.
Ah, not now.
Where's the food? Drink that. I hear a scary guy put torches.
That looks bad. What is that down there? Hold on. We gotta blow away through that.
Get away from me!
Wait, did my flaming maze just not become flaming when I'm in water? Look!
That's a neat little detail there.
Cool. Can I just launch this there somehow? Okay.
What if...
Wait, what? Dude, it's totally working though! Look!
I can break it sort of. Very weird functionality with the hammer here. I don't get it.
Shit, I can't launch it.
Oh god. Wait, we're fine. We're fine.
But I have an idea. I have an idea. I'm gonna get in through here.
Use this mode. Actually, I have a better idea. We're just going from the top.
That's way easier. There's also a heart here, actually. Hold on.
Can I destroy this?
Smashing puppet! A horrible chill goes down your spine. I don't like that.
Let me see here.
What? Quickly undertaker!
Hold your horses now!
Brisk shackle! Bro, I should be looking at my goddamn... Why can't I? Is it like a...
Oh, maybe I can only have one shackle.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. Look. Okay, gotcha. A burger!
Wait, it was 99 cents.
Also, Abigail is just killing things.
Let me use the regeneration potion. Sure, why not? It's used. I need to try this weapon, dude.
Are you kidding me right now?
It's an actual fucking gun! Oops, there's no way! Didn't I get a heart just now or something?
I'm losing my mind.
Oh god, oh god!
For now, equip this on two.
Because I don't trust the weapon yet. Oh, the gun? I haven't tried it really.
20.
Oh god. Abigail, Abigail. Oh god, oh god! I'm actually gonna die here. H.
Okay, focus.
Holy shit, that was a lot of enemies.
We're fine though. Can I shoot this stuff?
Oh no!
I hate these things. I'm gonna be ready here. Come on.
I think it's coming now.
Yeah, here it comes. Yeah, there it is.
All right, I'm gonna go upstairs now and lodge a bomb into the lake.
And are these enemies respawning?
Yo, the gun is sick!
Look at that shit! Oh, I love it!
I love the gun!
Armor cloud in a bottle.
Double jump!
No fucking way!
I'm missing... sure.
Get rid of that shit.
Give me this.
Oh god.
Dude, this is insanity. I love this.
I'm loving the items I'm finding here.
I wonder if this goes through enemies.
Can I stand here and just plunk?
I can just stand here and plink away!
Fucking love it.
Keep going down, dude.
We are going down into the depths.
Wait, we need this heart over there.
Let me shoot this guy.
Dude, this gun is insane.
And we're probably rich as fuck as well.
14 gold, dude.
Oh, we can double jump! That's so incredible!
Oh, I gotta get used to that.
Get up.
This is so easy now.
Recall potion.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Wait, another one.
Wow.
So, there's another heart.
And what are these things?
Maybe they spawned the enemies, actually.
Let's test something here.
Whoops.
Oh, that's fine, actually.
Oh, is that gonna destroy my screams echo around you?
I don't know if I like that.
Crimson rod.
I think I just got a bunch of items.
Dude, I can blink away from distance.
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
Oh, there's not infinite ammo?
Oh, you're shitting me.
Well, that was a little bit too good to be true, I guess.
That was insane.
That weapon was incredible.
Okay, we gotta heal.
I wish these enemies would let me have a moment to breathe here.
I kind of just want to look at my inventory and take stock, you know?
Nice.
Okay.
Abigail...
Can I de-summon Abigail here?
How about you go away, Abigail?
What if I write...
Oops.
That's not what I wanted.
So, what did I get?
A sharp tungsten axe.
Wait, no, I already had that.
Oh, shit, here we go.
Oh, I'm dead.
Poof.
What did I get?
I got...
I should go back, I think.
I really should go back.
You know what?
Let's...
No, I'm gonna eat a burger next time.
Next time I take damage, I'm gonna eat that burger.
There's something here that I want to take.
So, let's throw away this mud block.
In fact, I'm gonna put it...
Can I just click on the chest, actually?
Oh, I'm hitting the chest.
I get it, I get it.
Put away all the bullshit.
Pardon.
Sand block, we don't want that.
Sand block.
Vicious...
Sure.
Nice.
Okay.
New plan.
We are gonna...
Oh, this is what I'm gonna do here.
Oh, no, get away from me.
You asshole.
Okay, I got this item now.
Crimson rod.
Summon a cloud to rain blood on your foes.
Wait, does this have ammo again?
No, I wonder how I make ammo for that.
I wonder if it's just bullets.
There's arrows, there's flares.
There's probably bullets too, right?
That I can craft.
Oh my god, these fucking...
The blood moon is rising!
What does that mean?
I don't like that.
Eat the burger.
Okay, while that is happening,
I'm gonna bomb these fools.
Oh god.
Oh, no!
How am I alive?
Can we do it like that?
Bomb?
Here?
Go.
Right out of there.
Nice.
Do it again.
Look at this.
This is the pro strategy.
You see that shit?
Oh god.
Now we're getting closer.
Let's make it a little like that.
Yeah!
And we're in!
Brain of Ketul was awoken.
Oh what's that?
Heel!
Oh, I'm dead, I think.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What the fuck is happening?
Oh!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Brother!
I'm fucking dying here!
Oh, I'm so dead.
I can't heal anymore. Oh lordy. Holy shit. I dropped 11 gold.
God damn. That was scary. That was insane though. It was like a boss.
Brain of Cthulhu. Is that what a Cthulhu is?
Oh, what's the fuck is this now?
A tripler.
Oh no. Oh, wait a minute. Oh no, we have another incursion.
Is everyone okay? Joe? Joe is a little hurt. Otherwise, I think he's fine.
Abigail, do your thing.
You can't die now. I need to figure out how to make ammo for my gun.
Most incredible weapon ever.
Holder has defeated the 50th demon eye.
Damn right. I protect you, Joe. Oh goodness me.
What is making those bombs?
Okay, this weapon right here is actually kind of insane.
The mace is still really good. It's just so good.
What's that sound? Oh, they're knocking on the door.
Ho, ho, ho, ho. Line them up.
My God, I'm kind of OP right now. I'm being reminded of Zelda now with the blood moon.
That's probably what's happening here. That's what that is, man.
Come here. Oh, there's a guy. There's a lot of HP. There's so many enemies.
Joe. Survive, Joe.
Oh, wait. Is he? Joe is bombing them.
No, wait. This, of course. Demolitionist, he's bombing them.
I get it. Everything makes sense.
I'm taking a lot of damage here.
Come here.
Bro, the long range attack on this does a lot of damage. And it's nice.
Oh, God. Oh, no. Oh, shit.
I guess now is the test whether or not I can pick up my 11 gold I dropped down in the mine.
Oh, no.
Joe is dying. Oh, fuck off. Joe, please don't die. You've got this, Joe.
Oh, he's almost dead. Ralph died. Close these doors. Come on, Dawn, we need you.
I wonder if I can heal Joe. Nice.
Oh, okay. Looks like things have calmed. Zombie arm.
Hold on. You can knock on that door. That's fine. Close that shit.
Click this button. Crimson blood. I'm going to try this.
Oh, no. Did I just pick up ammo?
For some reason, I have ammo in my gun now. I don't understand what happened.
Heal. Oh, I'm actually dying. Oh, no. Don't engage that.
There we go. 20 and a half by dribbler.
Man, I don't understand this little thing here I made.
Is it going to do something when enemies walk on it? Let's see.
Just do shit.
Oh, God. Let's try again.
Where's the weapon? Demon eye banner.
I have full health. Crimson rod. Oh, I get it. Wow. Yo, that's insane.
Look at that. That's the perfect defense.
I love it. Oh, they don't last forever. Of course.
How do I... I was pressing my button for my mace. It didn't change for some reason.
I was spamming that button. I don't understand what just happened.
I need revenge on these fools. Oh, wait. I think I was in the menu. Oh, no. Goddamn.
Okay. I need to calm down here. I need to take...
Man, how long does this last? Oh, it looks like it's only raining gold when you're actually...
When there's actually enemies beneath it. And there's none right now. Let me put this here.
Fuck you. Shoot him out of the sky. Finally, dawn has come. Dude, this gun is wild.
I have to figure out how to make ammo for this and then I'm gonna make four billion ammos or bullets.
Oh, this gun is... All right, everybody. Let's take stock. Good job.
We lost Ralph, but otherwise it went great. You did well, everybody. You should be proud of yourselves.
Another demonic incursion has been held. Okay, wait.
I have two different undertakers. I wonder if I can...
Uh, Ralph. I mean, Joe. Ralph is dead. Joe, come here. Crafting.
Oh, I can't put it in there.
Bloody tear? Summons the blood moon? I don't want that. That seems terrible.
Don't go down here.
Can I craft anything special? Oops.
Where do I make bullets?
Oh, you know what? I should probably talk to the demolitionist. He would know things about bullets,
wouldn't he? Dynamite, my own special cure. Cure all for what ails you. I get you.
Hmm. Musket ball. That's it. Hold on.
Musket ball. Could I possibly make that? Did I miss it? Sticky bomb, coin, maybe here?
Crimtane bar. Uh, sure. Let's make one of those, I guess. Put it up there. Demon Eye Banner.
Bonus against... and I don't understand how this works. Oh! Oh! Oh, you hang it from a ceiling.
Wilbur! No way! Where you at? Hey, Wilbur, my dude. I have a room for you recently available.
Oh, you already moved in on your own, huh? Did I allow that? You fucker. Let's see what you got.
Uh, I hope a scrawny kid like you isn't all that is standing between us and get tool who's I.
Um, okay. Iron Anvil. I have that already. Flares and blue flares.
Man, how did I get those bullets? I guess I just got them from an enemy. Oh, I need to catch that.
What's up, squirrel? A red squirrel is now mine. Oops, don't shoot this thing.
Musket ball. Ammo. Okay, hold on. Well, how would you make this? I would say in a furnace, no?
You would smelt some molten iron or something. I'm gonna molten metal and shave it into small
balls, no? But maybe we can ask Joe. Musket ball probably made of... Do I have iron on me?
Or something like it? Let me grab some materials here. We're gonna do some testing.
Ores and doors? Sure. Ah, that's fine. Joe! How do I make musket balls?
Uh, crafting? Lead? Let's click on this one. No, where's the button for there? Oh, holy shit!
Wow! Oh, holy shit! Grave digger shovel. Can you dig it? Joe, this sounds insane.
I want that. What else can I make? Any musket balls? It doesn't look like it. Okay, uh, wait. Sawmill?
Blacksmith... Maybe I need this to... No, okay. Sawmill used for advanced wood crafting. I should
look for these descriptions here. Something like this is a utility item that I can place and
potentially craft new items, right? So I need to find something like that, but for making balls.
Like this... Used to craft items from metal bars. Let me actually go
to the anvil now that I have all my ores on me. Let's see. Anything? I can make a toilet.
Okay.
No, it doesn't look like it. Maybe here. Nope, not yet. Okay, Joe.
So, we can do a lot with the lead. I get it. What about tin? What can we make here?
We can make a watch or a staff. What about gold?
Jewelry and shit. And something... What is that?
Flings fur coat increases summon damage by five percent.
Oh, max number of minions. Summons a snow flings to fight for you.
Dude, I am intrigued by everything I'm seeing. It's insane.
Wait!
Yo, this is... This is the next level!
Cryptane!
Yo, 12 of them. Oh, no. Tissue samples. Do I have that?
Tissue. I have crim stone blocks. What can I do with that, Joe?
I can make crimtane bricks.
Crimson teeth wall.
But maybe crimtane bricks can be used to do something cool. Iron? Joe?
Okay, what about iron bar? Do I have that on me?
I have lead bar. Oh, we tried that already. Oh, did we? Or did we only try lead? Or?
No, we definitely... No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Flamethrower. New way. Okay, what's that? Leesian chest. Oh my god, dude. There are items in this game.
Holy shit. I wonder if this chest, like, has more space in it or something, or if it's just
cosmetics. A Dynasty bathtub. And a clock. A spooky clock. All right, all right.
Tin? Of course, tin bars. Platinum bars? Let's see.
I think I've already seen this, though.
Hold on. I have, you know what? I feel like musket balls. Hmm. Oh. Wait a minute, though.
Meteor shot. Oh, but they, oh wait, they require musket. Endless musket pouch!
Wait, I need 4,000? Hold on now.
Okay, so I need musket balls for all of this, but how do I make
basic musket balls? That's like the question, isn't it?
A crimtane. Sort the inventory, please. There we go. And now, lead, tin.
Okay. Let's say that was that for now with this. I'm gonna go put this back in the chest up.
What's that? A gold squirrel? Yonk?
That belongs to Mina. What's with all the squirrels?
Hey. Oh wait, I'm full inventory. Oh my god, what's happening?
Put things in chests. Did this squirrel just jump into the chest by itself? That's so weird.
What is, hold on, restock? Quick stack?
Goldfish. Let's put the organics back in here. Cloud in a bottle. This is wild,
but I already have one of these, so I should sell this. Also, this is one defense and 2%
melee speed. This is one... Yeah, I think I want this. Movement speed is nice, isn't it?
Risk shackle. Let's have that.
Now, the undertaker. Can I somehow enchant it to give it like an affinity like this? This is a quick,
you know, this is a quick version of it.
Uh, it doesn't say it can be upgraded with torches or something like the flaming mace set.
Okay, okay. Wars and doors. Let's quickly do this. Platinum in there and this and that.
Now I want to try tungsten. And maybe something simple such as stone. Maybe I can just use
stone to do this. Maybe I'm completely over... I feel like, so for a ranged weapon like that,
that needs ammo. You would need something very early game to make like bullets, right?
It wouldn't make sense otherwise to have something high level.
Tell me I can use this. Okay, here we go. Let's see. It's sort of roundish, isn't it?
Boulder? No, that's not it.
Useful smelting or let's see if there's more stuff like that here.
My goodness.
This is very overwhelming. There's a lot of shit. Damn. Oh, wait.
No, never mind. I can use tungsten to improve these musket balls.
Damn, I thought I just found it.
God damn it. Okay. Tungsten bullets, man. Can I...
All right. All right, all right. All right, Joe. Keep your secrets.
Also, I think it's a good thing we have this banner right here because when we have demonic incursions,
that's going to be very useful. What's up, bunny?
You're mine now. Thou ours to belong to me. Now, Wilbur, you don't sell any ammo?
Okay, okay, fine. Crafting.
With Galleous? Wait a minute. Didn't Galleous die? Am I crazy?
A water gun. Master Gamer's pants. Why does he have my pants?
Did you go through my dresser? I thought I told you to clean up your room.
Heart hairpin. Life form analyzer. Displays the name of rare creatures around you. What the shit?
Oh my god. Bro, I need to calm down for a second. Also, we have money in the cave
that we got to go retrieve. Okay, I'm gonna try one last thing here. I'm gonna take all of these
ores. Yeah, just the ores.
Because I have a feeling that's gonna make a musket bowl. Joe, look at this shit. Lead ore?
Oh wait, I tried this one already. So let's tin ore. Nothing there. Iron ore. Nothing. Platinum ore.
Also nothing. Tongsten. No. Obviously not gold. Gel? Hold on. What is this? Sticky bomb. Molotov cocktail!
Ale. Gel, silk. Oh, that's a lot of materials though. Sticky. Oh, that. See. Oh, sticky bomb.
That looks really useful. Can I just use a normal bomb?
A small explosion that will spread.
Yes! Bro, we're doing that. We're making half sticky, half normals.
The sticky ones is exactly what I need. That's great. I have shit on the gel. Holy shit.
It's time.
Sticky bomb, dude. We're gonna make half of this.
Actually, just make all of it.
Yeah, make all of it.
Hell yeah. Flaming arrow with... Oh, dude, totally.
Why not, right?
And then sort that inventory. I like the owl sound. Makes me happy. Ores and doors. Let's fill it up.
Okay, I definitely need to get a system going with my inventory where I just
immediately am able to clear out the bullshit, you know?
This right here is going to be a potion chest. Potions. Archery shine? I kind of want to bring that.
Spelunker? Kind of want to bring that. The crimson rod? I kind of want to bring that.
Do we have a... put this in here. Also that and this and this and I guess gel as well.
And go in there. Bloody tear. I think that's Michelinius, isn't it?
Let me put some of these in here as well.
Actually, they never dropped from my inventory, so there's no reason to put them in.
The axe. The fishing... oh, you know what? Let's go fish.
No, we're gonna go retrieve our items. We're ready. Let's move.
I'm gonna think about the whole bullet situation later.
Galeus has departed. Oh, he was a traveling merchant.
I feel like it wasn't Galeus one of the people who were here.
Like living? I guess not.
Give me that. The double jump is an actual game changer.
I could just ignore these, I guess. I mean, it's money, right?
I could try and fish, but it's the middle of the night and I'm scared.
Nice. So many stars.
He's on fire. Looks like there's a little chance of them catching fire.
Like it's not always. Oh, god. Oh, shit.
Nice. I kind of need Abigail here. Abigail, where are you at? I couldn't see it.
Did you see that pro game right there? That was pro.
Get him out of here. I need to heal. I need to upgrade Abigail somehow. It's not good enough.
You are not good enough.
Kind of fitting that my bomb is on the B key bind for bomb, you know.
Oh, god. Okay, okay. We're almost there.
Oh, I wonder if the boss thing is there still.
Well, I have my gun, so I have bullets for it. Close that shit off immediately.
Put more torches. Man, we went deep, didn't we?
Where do we go? We just went down.
Actually, it's not a bad idea to just have the map there.
Okay, here we are. Oh, god. We are fine.
Drink a lesser healing potion. What's that? Oh, that's just HP.
Did we loot this? I guess we did.
So it looks like the boss is gone.
Thankfully, let's grab the money.
Oh, thank goodness. We're back. And look at this now. Sticky. Yay!
Faster. Come on. There's so many. I need to figure out how to stop enemies from spawning.
This is actually a big issue of mine right now.
A horrible chill goes down your spine.
I hope that's bad, isn't it? Crimson heart?
Someone's a heart to provide light? What is this? Oh, it's a follower.
Oh, okay. I see. It's just bouncing around me. That's interesting.
This is going to get messy real quick. God, this gun is fantastic. I want to gun everything down.
Heal. What's all this? Nice. Very nice. So what I'm going to do now is this.
Open the floodgates.
And we're going to open more floodgates.
Just be careful there.
Oh, no.
All right. That's good. Man, we're killing it right now. This is easy.
I'm kidding. It's not easy. It's actually very hard.
But it feels good when I say it out loud like that. Makes me almost believe it, you know?
Torches everywhere.
What is it? It's a blue jellyfish. How did that get placed there? Oh, it's this automatic thing.
I get it. Dude, I'm going to keep going down. I don't even care.
Yo, I love the bombs. The bombs are so much fun. It's a legit way to mine things.
Reminds me a little bit of Bomberman. That game was the tits.
Just throwing bombs everywhere. And there's so many of them too. It has so many. What's that up
there? Careful here. Oh, it looks like loose rock. That's dangerous if I get that in my head.
Also, what's that up there? Is something going to fall on my head here?
Please no. Piranha. Go across here. I want that.
Then we have some tin. Yes. Now I'm not stopping there, dude. No way. We're going further down.
Straight down, baby. Yep. Even further. Oh god. Be careful!
Okay, we're going to drain this shit now. I love drain.
Look at that. Isn't that satisfying?
Look at this. Okay, didn't quite work as I intended. That's okay. I should use my thingy. This one.
Let's do like this. And then this is so genius.
Look at that. Such a great discovery that I can just hold the button there on it.
We've got some shit going on here. Let's do it. Oh, that's a big explosion. Dang.
Got all kinds of things there. See, I'm so lazy. I don't want to mind this. I just want to blow it up.
Oh. Oh, yeah. For a second, I thought I destroyed the... or... but I can definitely pick it up.
Oh, we even have platinum. Yeah. I want to find more of that crimson shit.
Whoa. A salamander. Shoot that shit.
He dropped potato chips. What is bro doing eating potato chips in the cave?
Betcha can't eat just one. 25 minute life regeneration.
Yep. We're eating chips in the cave. Mom's not here to stop. Oh.
Whoa. Yep. That's mine. Yonk. Thank you very much. Oh, we've got a centipede thing.
Bro, it's coming. Oh, almost had it. Let's jump down here. Also, we are deep right now.
There we go. There it is. Nice.
What? The boulder rolled into me underwater. I was ganged by boulder? Motherfucking boulders.
I need to figure out a way to prevent those deaths. That is terrible. Do we still have...
Oh, wow. This banner has a huge aura. That is no joke.
Okay. I need to test something here. How long does the cozy fire? What is the range on this?
Quickly. Let's do a quick deposit.
There. Good stuff. Oars and doors. In. In. And... what's this?
Bloodcrawler banner. I will be using that. Also, it just occurred to me. When I was fighting the
boss, I could have just used this to escape. I was totally fucked. I could have used that.
I'll remember that for next time.
Gills? I don't... I don't think I want that right now. I don't want this either.
Keep the mushrooms.
This one is in here.
I need to use my bow as well, actually.
I'm not using that.
Okay. I think we're ready. I need to use these potions. I keep forgetting that I have them.
It's a problem. My dude. What do you sell again? Right. An actual bomb.
Okay. I feel like I should get rid of these.
I don't like them here. This is making me uncomfortable. It's bringing up some memories.
Memories that are not happy memories.
Put them in there.
All right, Joe. And everyone else. See you later. What was your name? Mortal.
I don't remember you. Are you new here?
But this heart right here is... I don't know if I like that. It looks like a little butt.
That follows me around.
Makes me feel like whatever happens, I'm the butt of the joke.
Hey. Whoa, we were sitting on some money there.
Gave me that money.
One enemy nearby? Scorpion! Wait.
Yank! You were mine. 10% bait power. Oh, the one time I put my fishing rod away.
You're kidding. I need to try this, by the way. What the fuck is this shit?
Well, that did exactly as I expected it. Amazing. That's amazing.
See you, bitch.
Man, I always feel like I am closer than I actually am. I actually went pretty far
before I went down.
And I chose a diff... I chose a really difficult cave here as well.
Because there are these fucked up animals everywhere here.
These demons. Excuse me, sir.
You mad, bruh? Jump! Jump! Come on! There we go. A vertebra. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my goodness. Yeah, we have to go right.
But I guess we could just dig. We could just dig through everything. We can destroy every single block.
I gotta remember this. But let's just go this way. There's no reason not to.
Can I go this way then? Uh-oh.
Yes, I did. Oh god. What am I doing?
Okay, you know what? That works, actually. This is fine. There's a bit of a waste there.
Cave bad. I want you. Oh, that doesn't work. Oh, you motherfucker. That's an enemy.
It's witches everywhere. Okay, we're soon here.
Man, how do I spot these damn rolling boulders before they kill me?
Oh, wait, I thought that was a... Thank you. Oh, come on. Oh, what's happening?
I gotta eat. Also, drink that shit. Let's get some light in here. And also, can I just drink anything?
Okay, that's way more effective than I thought it would be. Holy fucking shit.
Are you kidding me? Holy crap. That's insane. I'm getting all this.
Oh, I even see like vases and stuff above me. How long does that last? Five minutes?
You know what? We're on the time pressure here, so I'm gonna be blowing shit up instead.
Boink. Yeah. Do it like that.
Oh, yeah. We don't care. I love these explosions. I love bombs.
The double jump is insane. Okay, that's fine. That's fine. Also, where's my gold? Did I get my gold?
I did 18 gold. I am freaking rich.
Yeah, I just go this way, I guess. Dude, I'm gonna dig down. I can't tell what... I think this is...
Actually, I can't tell. I think this is platinum down there. Fuck you. Oh, no.
Please die, thanks. Oh, it's lead. Okay. Oh, yeah, oh, yeah. Dude, you can go deep in this game. Wow.
Dirt block? Uh, fine. Now that's, uh, I think amethyst.
What's that? Why is it shaped like that? Oh, it's just stone.
No, wait, silt. Weird. Uh, green. Wait, you're gonna lead me somewhere. Why did you arrive?
Lead me to the promised land. The blood moon is rising. Oh, no. I wonder if stuff is
being simulated back at my house right now while I'm here. If I just stay here, will my fucking
people die? Okay, it's leading me to the left. Let's just go. I'm coming. I like this song.
Hey, fairy man. I'm coming.
I have so many light sources. I have my helmet. I have this heart. I have this potion and I have,
uh, that's pretty much it. Oh, oh, I see something over there. Is that gold?
Come on. Is that what it's leading me to? I forgot what it led me to last time.
Oh, oh, it's leading me to a heart. Fantastic. Let's fucking go.
Oh, I, I really need that because I die a lot in this game. Any help I can get, I'll take it. And
that's blood dripping down up there. Man, I hate this butt. It's just pooping all the time.
It displeases me. Give me all this stuff.
Yep. Oh, look at this beauty. Oh, it's gonna disappear in five seconds.
That potion is incredible. I need to figure out how to make that.
Let's fucking go. How much do I have now? 200 HP. That's double from what I started with.
That is just great, isn't it? Even the butt is excited.
Oh, yeah. Give me all that.
Okay. Where do I go now, though? That's the question. Why can I not zoom with my
mouse wheel? That's a bit annoying.
What's this? Oh, it's just like a default zoom level, it seems. Whoops, I didn't mean to shoot that.
Wait, what? What's happening? Get away from me. Eat this. I'm hearing enemies now.
I'll just grab this stuff up here. Oh, I need to activate this mode again. God damn it. There we go.
Where are the enemies? I think I hear them to the left. Where's this green stuff?
It's just stone, mossy stone.
Dude, I'm getting a ton of lead, but that's good because did you see how many recipes involved the lead?
It was like a million. Let's go this way now. I think I see something.
Yeah, that's a treasure. Drop some money, that's nice.
Bro, the flare is actually really good. I have no idea where I'm going right now.
I'm following the sounds. I hear water. What am I seeing?
Something's happening here. Oh, that's dangerous.
Okay, that's not good. You got to get up like this. Yeah, look at that. That's how you do it.
Oh, careful here.
This is bad. Okay, I have an idea actually. I have a great idea.
What if I... Oh, I can't block it with... Okay. Well...
Okay, new plan. Here's the new plan. I'm gonna say fuck it and we're just gonna go down.
Oh, there's sand everywhere there. No, no, no, no, that's bad. Sand is bad.
How did I get up here if I can't go down? I don't understand.
Okay, we'll go all the way to the bottom here and then we keep going down.
Oh, that's a river of blood right there.
There we go. I wish I could get some kind of a way to swing across like tar sand.
I feel like worms, you know. That would be amazing. Okay, now go this way.
Unless you're healing, nice.
And what is this right here? Sapphire! Ooh, that's gotta be worth a lot.
Am I rich? Actually, I am. Look at this. I have 18 gold.
I can pretty much buy anything when that merchant comes back around.
Uh-oh. Don't you fucking come close to me and make that sound. Violent depth meter!
Huh? Displays depth. Oh, seven. Oh, cool. That's kind of neat.
Blow that shit up. Uh-oh, wrong, wrong throw.
Make a hole through there and drain the shit out of this. Oh, that is so satisfying.
What is that? It's a crawdad? What the fuck is a crawdad?
I don't know what that means. Looks like a crap to me.
Oh, what the fuck? We've got a fire centipede.
Oh, nice. What did I get? Maybe nothing. You know what? Why don't we have this?
We should be using Abigail. Skeleton! Oh, we've got another one of these!
Man, they're so scary.
Okay, we're going deep here. I need to scratch my ear. Okay, I will utilize my one and only...
Oh, I don't have a lot of web rope, but I have a shit ton of rope. Beautiful.
And then we just do this. Look, I can just hold it here. Lovely.
And that's the depth we go to. Is that a trap?
No.
Close. Recall potion, that's nice.
Okay, grab all of this as well.
Tungsten, we have been mining for a long time now.
But I feel like I'm committed. I need to go deeper, deeper and deeper and deeper.
I need to see what's at the bottom. The curiosity is killing me.
Let's go like this now.
Let's bomb the shit out of it. Catch breath. I can catch breath in that tiny moment.
Yep, keep going.
Okay, full breath, nice.
Oh, this is getting a bit scary here. I need to catch my breath.
Nice. I hear enemies to the left.
Wait, did I just see some light when it exploded around?
Oh, I should utilize that. Uh-oh. I hate those things.
Fucking die. Oh my god.
Nice. Okay, we're fine, we're fine. I think it's fine. Where the fuck are we right now?
Anything on this side here? I mean, uh, man, I'm actually running out of bombs. I should save them.
Maybe I don't want to dig here because there's water. Let's continue digging on the right side.
Or the left side, I mean.
More sapphire. Hell yeah, dude. Does it say anything special? Can be placed? Material? Okay.
Right on, dude. I should dig through the dirt because it's quicker.
Speaking of dirt, we could make a shovel as well. That would dig a larger area,
but if it's only if it's soft. So that's interesting, isn't it?
Oh, this is shitty territory here.
Why is the music changing to something scary?
What's happening?
I don't like the sound of this. Oh, I see light in the bottom left.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, hello. Wait, what's that sand slime?
Isn't that interesting?
Desert torch. Oh, we're some kind of desert cave here now.
Oh, god. Oh, they have a lot of HP, 160. Antlion mandible.
Okay, okay, sure, sure. Oh, I have an idea here. I have an...
Get up. Love that there's background here. Look at this.
Is that pro or what? I'm just gonna sip my drink while I watch these enemies dissipate.
Oh, yeah.
You like that? Giant Antlion Charger 220 HP, bro. That's a lot of shit. Oh, god.
What's that? Oh, I knew something would come out of it. I fucking knew it.
Hey, you. Oh, there's something down there. Rain on these fools.
What if I destroy this now?
Ah, look, now it has free rain to kill it. That is beautiful.
Killed. I think there's a chest down there.
Encumbering stone prevents item pickups while locked.
You are what?
Storm Spear. Sure. Just take everything.
Healing potions. Night increases Nightwish. Let's try. Oh, that's nice.
Invisibility.
What? Two gold coins as well? Oh, that's fire. Oh, that's bad. I almost died just now.
We don't like that. We don't like that. That needs to be blocked off.
Nope. No, no, no, no, no, no. We don't want none of that. What's that in the...
Something's moving around in the fire.
Oh, wait, this is my fucking heart. Never mind.
I thought the fire was alive for a second there. Get out of here.
I need to heal. Let me take this chest with me.
Wait, I have no more... How do I... Did you see that pro dodge? Oh my god, I'm actually dying here.
Uh, I could... Oh no! Where did you come from? You motherfucker. I was just about to heal.
God, dang it. Well, that was a good run though. Holy shit, we discovered a bunch of stuff.
That was nice. That was really fun. Okay, it's time to check out all the stuff we got, huh?
This is a nice part. First, we click this button here.
Everything goes in. It's so good. What a feature.
Wait. Oh! Prevent... Prevents item pickups well locked.
I guess that's smart if you really don't want to pick anything up at all.
Uh, but yeah, okay. Put it in. Um, what's this? Hook.
Sometimes dropped by skeletons and piranha.
Okay. Okay, with all these new items, let's go check with Joe.
Hey, Joe! What can I make with this stuff?
Sturdy fossil.
Scarab bomb.
Narrow explosion that will destroy most tiles.
Explosion aims away from your precision.
Oh, and a pickaxe. Not a very good one, though. Javelin.
Ambers, hold on. Foss, wait. How good is my armor? It's actually pretty sick. Five defense?
Oh man, my boots are shit. I really need to make new boots. Wow. Yep. Definitely.
Uh, hook.
Grabbling hook.
Wait, I can make that. I have chain. I have chain!
Uh, chain, chain, chain. Where is the chain? There it is.
Wait, sapphire hook? Requires sapphires. Is that better? It sounds better. Let's make it.
And, you know what? That wasn't said. I think this is a big thing because, uh, grapple?
No. Oh my god. No way.
Damn. That is a great thing. Holy shit.
Bloodcrawler banner. Dude, this makes me so excited right now. Do I have to have it in my inventory?
Probably, right? I'm just gonna test. I mean, maybe not, because there's a key... Yeah, okay, I need it.
Gotcha. Okay. That's a great development.
Um, almost makes me feel like we don't need the rope anymore.
Put that in there. Okay, Joe! That was awesome, Joe. What else can I make, Joe?
Can I do anything with this? Uh, sapphire. Ooh, here we go.
Is that sapphire gemlock? Blue faceplate?
Meteorite! I wonder how I get that from meteors fragments, but that would be on the surface, no?
Sapphire's large sapphire. For capture the gem, it drops when you die.
Okay. Wait, sapphire gemcord?
Gemcord? Are you saying I can plant this shit? What's the point of a blue torch?
Yo, this is awesome. I kind of want to make things... Uh, what can I do with chains, Joe?
What? Oh, my chains. Joe, hold on. Chains? Oh, what? Okay!
Oh, these are all chandeliers. Damn, there are many of them. Chestlock. That's actually pretty cool.
Okay, these are all just chandeliers.
Huh. Um, wait. Oh, I need a life crystal for this.
This seems like a pretty useful, uh, item. If it means I can pick it up again and take it with me.
Not bad, Joe. What about the scorpion, Joe?
Oh, no. Can I make a scorpion cage? Terrarium? I don't know why. That's like, that's what this game is.
Uh, okay, you can't do anything with that. What about this?
Wait a minute. Potion of return! Teleport you home and create a portal.
Use portal to return when you are done. What? Obsidian fish?
Hold on a sec. We gotta go fishing. Immediately. Uh, hold on, Joe. What about sandstone? Sandstone?
What was it? Here. I can make a wall. Antlion eggs. Uh, I can make that. You know what? Let's try that.
I want to see if I can get a pet antlion. Where is it?
Wait, hold on. I feel like I'm missing some basic crafting stations here.
Uh, there's just, I have the items for that, but I can't craft it.
So, I'm missing something basic here, I think.
I need to look at basic, uh, stuff. Do I have sand on me? What is silt?
Gray stucco. What the? Okay, well, I guess I checked most of these things now.
Hmm. So, I have an anvil, I have a crafting bench, and a furnace. And then we have this thing,
which will allow me to do certain things, I guess. But not with the items I have in my inventory currently.
Let's see. What could I possibly use? Bring this. We're gonna go fishing. So, that means organics.
Uh, bait power. Here we go. Wait! Ammo? Ammo? Hold on a sec.
Wait a minute. Joe! Can I do something with gel? I feel like I've asked him this before, but...
Gel? Where's my gel at? God, I cannot find my way around this inventory. I swear to God.
Did I even bring the gel? For fuck's sake. I think I left it up here, didn't I?
Huh? Oh wait, it's here. Never mind. Fuck. It's so dumb. Uh, right. Give me that.
Okay, Joe. Tell me again what I can do with this. Right, it was this stuff. Hmm.
Yeah. Why is it considered ammo, though? That's what's interesting to me right now.
You there. I'm gonna sell you some stuff. Take that. And take...
Do you want some silt? No, I'm gonna keep that, actually. Okay, this is actually worth quite a lot.
Now, my question now is, what if I take some wood? Because wood is like a basic crafting ingredient.
Let's take all kinds of different forms of wood here.
And let me just ask Joe what I can do with wood. We're gonna go back to basics here.
Let's see. Okay, here we go. Now, this looks promising. Heavy workbench! Motherfucker! Cooking pot!
Now we're talking!
Fireplace! Yes, dude! Okay, well, any iron bar. Gotcha. I can do that.
Wait. Iron? Why do I not have any iron ore?
I've been mining forever! How is that real? Okay, I'm gonna try something here.
Just take everything. How do I make...
smooths... wait.
Platinum lead. And I make with... oh, okay. I can actually make a bunch here. What can I make?
Wait, I can make this? Wait, any iron? Okay, what counts as iron, then? Let's see.
Lead! And also, tungsten was moving. I saw these two change. Okay, here we go! It's finally time.
Put it there. Okay.
So, what was it that I wanted to try and craft before? Give me that.
Get in there. Wait, this is not organics. Goddamn it. You're free. You're free.
Also, make all the bars. Damn, that's a lot. Very nice.
Uh, here. Tungsten. And I hold shift and... I wish I would just automatically put it in there.
It's a bit confusing to me. Let me make one smooth sandstone.
I want to show it to Joe. Joe, look what I did to the sandstone.
All kinds of stuff with sandstone, to be expected, I guess.
But, Ralph, you... wait. Oh, it's because I'm next to this thing right here.
I was like, why can I now craft all kinds of things? But that explains it. That explains it.
Man, I need to figure out what this hammer is actually used for.
Okay, what can I make right now? Am I close enough to...? Oh, did I see a...
mine cart? Trash can? Glass kiln? Oh, hell, yeah, dude.
Probably not the best place to put this, but this is all temporary. We're experimenting.
I have big plans to make a proper house. Something grandiose and fantastic.
It's gonna be glorious. But for now, I'm just chilling.
Heavy workbench done. Bath tub. I'm totally gonna make a bathroom. Heck, yeah, dude.
How about we make some better shoes? Because our shoes suck.
Why can't I not make platinum shoes? Oh, I can probably make tungsten.
Tungsten. Greaves. Let's do that.
Fuck these wooden shoes. They can be destroyed. I kind of forgot that I have a delete button here,
actually. The iron ore. Let's delete that as well, because it's annoying me. This is also annoying
me. I'm gonna make any more bars with this. It doesn't look like it. Okay, now click this
button here. Okay, there's nothing to put in. Gotcha. These fucking squirrels are annoying me.
Here's a question.
If I have items in my chest here, will I be able to craft things with them when I
don't have them in my inventory? It don't... Wait, am I actually lead bar? No, I have lead here.
Hold on. See, that would be a killer feature if you were able to do that.
Let's see here. Let's try and put this in here. We're testing. And now? Yeah, no, you can't.
That would be pretty insane, wouldn't it? Yeah, I think it's worth it to invest time into making a
proper, um, organizational room and setup from the very beginning. Because otherwise,
this is what's gonna happen, just like Minecraft. I keep telling myself, oh, I'm gonna be fixing
all the organization later. And before I know it, I've already spent a hundred hours and I never
fucking did it. So you know what? It's freaking time. I'm gonna do this properly now. Let me
grab all this first. Give me that. Thank you. Awesome. So for that, I'm gonna need wood. I'm
gonna need stone. Basic materials here. Let me clean my inventory a bit. A goblin army is approaching
from the west. Okay, hold on. Hold the phone. Um, stuff is happening here. We're under attack.
Hold on now. This ain't good. What should I, uh,
from the west? Close the door. Actually, I have an idea. This is the genius play right now.
Where's the stone? Give me stone. Where's the stone?
There. What are you gonna do now? Goblin army?
The goblin army has arrived. Oh, oh, oh. Sorcerer. Oh, they're in our house.
This is bad news. Look at that wall I made. The wall is paying dividends.
That magic, though, scares me. Dodge that shit. Heal.
Nice. We're doing well so far. Let's kill the sorcerer. Oh my god. Look at all the sorcerers.
Okay, they're low HP, though. That's something. Oh, I need epic. No!
Okay, that's crazy. Look how many there are.
Looks like this guy is doing well, though. Hano.
And Joe is keeping this archer at bay, it seems.
Somewhat. Mortal. Let's go. Also, we're gonna deploy Abigail.
Oh, god. The archer is killing me. Why can't I hit shit?
Oh!
Bro, I'm... this is... this is crazy. The arrows are killing me.
Oh my god. Dutch! No, no, no. There's no way I'm surviving this shit. I am done for, bruh.
Holy fuck. No! What the fuck? Damn. This is insanity. Wait, what? What did they say? Goblin thief?
There's doing my gold? Back to the house!
Back to the house. Deploy this.
Oh my god! Oh, no! This is terrible. Are they stealing my money?
This thing is doing work, though. I'm liking that. I'm liking that. In fact...
Oh, I'm dying. Put this anywhere. Just kill me, dude.
Damn. Wow. Holy shit. They are not fucking around.
Fuck. Oh my god. Oh, are you kidding me? Bro, this is insanity! How am I supposed to survive this shit?
I need... I need... can I fix my inventory while I'm dead? I can't.
Like, I can't escape here. I can shoot them, at least.
Man, that's not doing shit. Fuck it. Leave!
Oh my god. Oh, wow! Oh, I think I've lost all my money. All my money is freaking gone.
Okay, now they're all onto the west, though. I can go this way. Oh, no! We're graveyarding now!
Oh, wait. Where's my... my hook? Oh, this is just terrible.
Just fucking kill me, dude. Oh my god. Where's my hook?
What? Where did I put it?
Oh, man. I was trying to go into the roof. Man, Hano is killing it right now. That guy's a beast.
We need rain. Look at this guy. He's flying around the screen. No, I'm dead, bro.
I don't know what to do. I don't know what's happening, dude.
Oh, this is kind of nice. You get to see what's down in the cave when he shoots the spell.
Joho! Oh, this is a disaster. Are you kidding me? Kill these fuckers.
I'm running out of bullets here. Oh my god. Just go. Oh, this is a full-blown disaster.
Remove that map. Like, I feel like I'm stuck in a cycle here where I can't really do anything.
Like, are these guys going to not spawn anymore soon? I don't know what to do.
I'm getting my ass kicked. Come on. Let me get back into this.
I kind of want a shield or something that can block projectiles. I feel like that's what I
need here because these archers and these mages are impossible to do anything about.
Wait, actually. Wait, I'm destroying projectiles with this. I just realized.
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. I may have discovered the secret to this.
I think I get it now. We need jungle, I'm afraid.
Uh, weed the ruthless flaming mace. And we just got to keep swinging. Just keep swinging.
That's the secret here. Oh, not. Oh my god. This is terrible. Now it's also thundering.
Bro, this is changing everything now that I know this about the projectiles.
Does it work against arrows as well? It doesn't. Okay. Which against spells? Not arrows.
Oh my god, that guy has HP.
Damn. He's armored to the teeth.
Fucking die. Come on. Okay, now. Oh, okay. Recoup. Recoup.
Uh, regroup. I mean, fucking lock it off. Where'd you come from?
Okay. Damage control. And now we do this. There we go.
Oh, youth. Oh, he's the mages down here. I need to heal. I need to heal. Five seconds.
Come on. Heal up. Nice. Oh, no.
I see the issue here. There we go. Ha ha. That's much better. That's how we do it.
Oh, that's so effective.
That is what we need. We need Abigail. Oh, yeah, look at that.
Fuck all of y'all. Piss off my property. Oh. Oh, that's unfair. I can't get to him.
Wait, did he teleport? Where'd he go? Oh, god. Oh, god. I didn't mean to be here.
Damn. Okay, back to business.
Look at these freaking assholes here. The arrows are killing me. Those are the biggest issues.
Dodge it. Dodge it. Dodge it. Go! Oh, fuck. This is crazy. When is this ending?
This is not just a little bit of a raid. This is full-on invasion.
Everyone is joining this right here. The whole fucking army of Mordor has arrived.
Do I have bullets? I don't even have bullets left. This is really bad.
Okay, okay. So far so good. Wait, did they disappear?
Are we good? I need to grab my goddamn hook right now. Where is it?
Oh, there it is. It was right there.
Quick. Oh, I don't have any fucking things. So how does this work again? Oh my god, it's so good.
Can I do tricks like this?
Wait. Oh, that's a bit awkward. Oh, yeah, that totally works. Heal.
Fucking do that. Oh, I can only have a couple active at a time, it seems.
Okay, okay, okay, we're fine. We're fine. So these fools are still here, huh?
I need you. And then rain on these fools.
Okay, that works. Just kill them all. I think I lost all my money, man.
All my money is gone. While that is happening, I just want to...
Actually, let me go with all this. I want some of that money back.
Is everyone else over here doing fine? Fuck all of y'all. Oh, yeah.
Why is it not raining? There we go. Oh, that is lovely. Love seeing that.
Put them on fire down here. Oh, that is so satisfying.
Oh, there you go. See ya.
And then we kill them on this side, man. How long are they gonna stay here?
Is this something never ending? Is there spawn over here?
Does it mean I need to kill something to prevent them from coming?
I'm confused about that. I did it. Goblin punter. Well, that was very, very difficult.
Wow. That was insanity. I can't believe it. We gotta clean up this shit.
And then, man, we need to set up some defenses. This shit can't happen again.
This is a wake-up call. God damn wake-up call. Get out of here. Stupid ass ghost.
Let's get rid of all these tombstones. Yep. Okay, seems like the graveyard is gone.
Wait. Oh, I can't. I see now. I don't have inventory. God damn.
It's time to continue the plan here. Why is it... What's happening in the background?
Are we celebrating the victory? Are we just sending up lanterns here?
This is an absolute disaster, though. This is a very pyrrhic victory.
The costliest victory ever. Oh, god.
What's that? Oh, it's an owl. Okay, we're fine.
Wasn't there also an enemy down here in the cave?
Owl flew into the sky. That rains blood. That's hilarious.
Okay. Man, oh man. That was something else, wasn't it?
God damn. Let's clean up inventory, expand our house, and set up some goddamn defenses.
I want to experiment with the dart trap that I found as well.
A lot of stuff is gonna happen now. First, we sort our inventory. Bam, like that.
And then take all of this, put it in here for now, because we don't need it immediately.
And construction, uh, keep all the construction stuff here for now.
Wooden doors and all that. That's fine.
Michelinias, banners, and desert torches, and all this other bullshit.
No, this is organic. Hook.
To do scorpion is organic. This one is, can also go in here.
Silt block is... no. Put it there.
Mushrooms, it's organic. Put it in.
And like this one and that one.
Just clean everything. What is this?
The strong harpoon has...
The same damage as the normal harpoon, except it has 15% knockback.
What is this then?
That's a very odd sound effect, listen.
Almost sounds like fireworks going off in the distance when I shoot it.
Strong harpoon, huh?
A bunny.
Damn.
A squirrel. Damn.
Oh! Oh! Oh, cool!
Wait a minute now. That's a lot of damage.
Is that not really nice?
Let's get rid of all this.
And the way I get rid of this is use the hammer.
See, this I understand, I think.
Yeah, this is how you deconstruct walls. Use the hammer.
The hammer is a very curious item in this game.
Its function is a little mysterious to me.
I get the wall thing, but maybe that's just what it is.
It's just for background stuff.
You know, like background stuff like walls and other things.
Let me try this.
Oh, it's actually very...
Okay, if you don't hit anything, it's actually not great.
You need to hit.
Otherwise, you have to wait for it.
Yeah, that's really annoying.
But it does decent damage.
It definitely does decent damage here. It's very nice.
I can respect it.
I'm deconstructing all of this now.
There we go.
We have all of this.
We don't want any of this shit in our backyard anymore.
What's that?
Strong Abigail!
Hale's flower!
Wait a minute.
I have three of them.
Whoa, hold on.
Let me look at that later.
Okay, let's see here.
Six damage, six damage, six damage.
Very weak, very weak, very weak.
Not this one.
This one is best, I think.
Oh, shit.
Yup.
Oh man, the harpoon is actually nice.
If you're just attacking in a straight line like that,
it's really nice.
Oh my god.
Does it do damage on the return?
It does!
Man, oh man.
I'm starting to get a lightning for this thing.
What's hitting me?
Oh, you.
Come here, bastard.
God, it feels good to just kill things right now without dying.
200 zombies defeated, bitch.
I like the background, it's super nice.
That's gotta be celebration for what we did.
Oh yeah, we're getting all the money back.
We have seven gold, it's not bad.
And we also lost a bunch of gold in the cave.
Let's not forget that.
So it's actually not the end of the world regarding money here.
Most of that money is in the cave.
Yellow marigold.
I'm gonna kill things right now, dude.
Just clean up the entire graveyard here.
Any more headstones I need to clear out?
Or are we good?
Get away from me, I.
There's another one there.
Thank you.
Ah, will you stop that?
That's a green one.
Nice.
Oh, it dropped something.
Oh, they dropped the lens.
I think the zombies just keep coming.
I don't think the tortures do shit to prevent the spawns.
I think you need to do something else to prevent the spawns.
And it's gotta be related to housing.
Because they don't spawn on my house, right?
So what I'm gonna do actually, and I think this is smart,
I need to figure out what counts as housing.
So maybe I'll make like a fence.
And anything within the fence, maybe nothing will spawn.
Think about that for a second.
I am tired of these goddamn enemies in my ass.
They are in my bunghole and it feels bad.
It's a bad feeling.
Hey, bunny!
Why do so many bunnies?
That's what I want to know.
See, it's so peaceful here.
This is what I want everywhere.
Okay, let's get into construction mode.
What I'm gonna do...
Oops.
Let's put...
Where's my actual axe?
Did I put that in my chest?
Must have.
No, it would be in Michelinius.
Yeah, I did.
So let's replace that with that and then...
Oh man, I...
Yeah, remove the flare gun, I guess.
Put that in here.
Also the flares.
So these flowers here...
What's the best one I have?
It's this one.
Very weak knockback uses 10 mana.
They all use 10 mana.
Put these two in here.
What if I put this in now?
Abigail still stays.
So you can actually summon one and then go exploring.
To clear up an inventory slot.
That's actually pretty nice information there.
But it's good to have on you.
So gravestones and stuff, they go in here.
And what's it here?
Yeah.
Oh, these are statues.
But I guess I have obelisks and stuff.
What just happened?
Do do.
Yellow marigold.
What?
Wait, Seymour?
Wait a minute, we lost Joe.
Is that the new Joe?
Seymour?
Sword beats paper.
Get one today.
No, you're not the new Joe.
Do we have a new Joe?
Seymour?
Mortal?
No, we don't.
Oh no.
He's gonna respawn though, right?
Just like Maxwell respawned as Joe.
I think we're fine.
We just need to wait.
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
Okay.
Bum bum.
Oh, this is the one with the...
Put them in here instead.
Armored shackle.
Plus three defense.
Yo, that's pretty sick.
This one sucks.
Romeo the traveling merchant.
Oh no, I don't have money now.
Why does they always arrive when I don't have money?
God damn it.
I mean, this one is pretty useless now that I already have one.
So I guess I'll sell it.
All the things I sell go here.
Michelinius.
I should have a chest just called materials.
But then again, almost everything in this game counts as a material.
No.
This quick stack.
Hold on, what is...
What is quick stack actually?
Does that just put whatever I have in my inventory into the chest and stacks it?
I think it does.
Let's put that in there.
Let's put the silt in here.
I feel like I've looked at this stupid silt block for...
You know what?
Fuck off.
I hate the silt block.
Spiky bowl?
Wait.
Oh no, I thought it was...
I thought it was ammo.
God damn it.
Equip your first grappling hook.
Didn't I do that though?
Wait.
Equip it?
Why do I not?
Maybe I need to...
Maybe the sapphire one doesn't count for whatever reason.
I want to try something.
I have chains.
Michelinius.
Oh, I have them here.
Craft.
Let's just make a grappling hook.
How do I equip it?
Oh, over here?
I get it!
I see.
We can have a...
Oh, wait.
Does that mean I can put a bunny there, for example?
Let's put a golden s...
Nope.
Wait.
Uh, no?
Maybe that doesn't count as a pet?
Squirrel?
Can I have a pet squirrel?
Huh.
Visible?
Oh, nice!
I can hide the heart.
That's... you know what?
Hide that shit.
I don't want to look at it.
But does it still provide light?
It doesn't.
What's the point of hiding it?
Oh, man.
Crimson rod!
Someone's a cloud to rain blood on your foes.
Wait, this is the one I already have.
No, mind.
That's not new.
I want the sapphire one.
That's cooler, though, isn't it?
Get over here.
Actually, I think I'll like this one more.
Am I crazy?
Yeah, I definitely like this more.
It's less intrusive on the UI here, for me.
So, and that means when I sell this to people,
he's probably gonna love it.
39 silver?
That's for you.
That's color on it.
You love colors, don't you?
Headstones?
What's in here?
A marpoon.
All the construction stuff is here on purpose.
I guess I need it now.
Mudblock, tin.
Do we have a shit ton of wood somewhere?
Oh, yeah, we have it on us.
Okay, perfect.
Good.
Wood and stone.
We have both of these.
That's for construction.
We have wood walls.
Everything is ready, I think.
Rope and the potions.
I guess this can also go in here.
The gel is Michelinius.
Yeah, why not?
Okay.
Cloud and a bottle?
I want to sell that.
Hey, Hanno.
Nope, actually.
Romeo!
Wait, are you the one?
Combination hookah and coffee maker also makes julienne fries.
I don't know what that means.
Dynasty wood.
50 gold?
Bro, I don't want that.
That's terrible.
Do you want this?
Oh, that's one gold.
Hell yeah.
You can also have this shitty door.
What about some spiky balls?
No, I'm keeping those.
They look cool.
Put the spiky balls in here for now.
Wait, I have a strong heart.
Oh, I can sell that one.
Romeo, do you want this?
54?
Nice.
Wait, do they disappear?
Hold on.
Oh, they disappear after I sell it.
Okay.
Interesting.
Utilities there.
I think we're about ready to do things.
So how do I do this?
How should I do this?
It wouldn't be a terrible idea to have something underground.
You know?
That would be a very nicely fortified position.
I also want to build a sort of spot up here
where I can shoot down on the enemies easily.
I want to have traps and shit.
A nice lookout, you know?
You know those little holes in ancient castles
where the archers would stand and shoot out of?
And be protected?
Something like that.
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm going to level this ground right here.
Let's remove this.
And level this out here.
Man, the hammer is...
And now I can't...
What the fuck?
I don't get it!
Mysterious is what it is.
Get rid of this tree as well.
Let's fill this up with earth.
Oh, I have to remove this.
Nope.
Whoops.
Wrong button.
There we go.
Look at this.
Nice fundamentals.
And then we get rid of...
Can I remove this like that?
Nice.
Take this now.
All these stupid gravestones.
Get rid of them.
Oh, do we have more stupid gravestones?
We have one over here as well.
Clean that shit up.
There's a gun there!
Sell this harpoon.
Hey!
This is better!
Awesome!
See more.
You would like the normal harpoon.
There you go.
You know what?
I should just give these stupid tombstones.
Why am I keeping them?
I should just destroy the tombstones.
Tombstones suck.
Wait, obelisk?
Is that a tomb?
I think it's a tombstone.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, yeah, it's probably a tombstone.
Sword items.
Destroy all this crap.
We don't want to be reminded of what happened there.
The dart trap.
I feel like I need a pressure plate for that to activate it.
Let's actually experiment with that.
I think we have one.
Pressure plate? No.
Brown pressure plate activates when a player steps on it.
Oh, when a player steps on it?
Not the enemies?
Okay, it's definitely activating something.
Okay, let's try something.
Yeah, how would I connect it, right?
Maybe if I just...
Maybe it's just a range thing.
Because down in the cave, I couldn't see the pressure plate for that trap anyway.
So maybe if something is within a certain range, it just always activates.
But maybe it doesn't activate on me because I placed it.
So it's recognizing me as like the good guy, you know?
Now we'll see.
I'm gonna try and put it over here for now.
Put it like there.
So that way it shoots this way if they come this way.
Okay, nice.
Let's also fill this up.
Make it look nice.
Like that.
Let's make this a bit nicer as well.
Rid of all this crap.
What's that?
That's fine, I think.
This looks nice.
Okay.
And I like the way the banner sways when I walk past it.
We're gonna expand the shit out of this house.
That's what I'm talking about.
This is gonna be our crafting room.
Yep.
Perfect.
And then we use this.
Oh, I hate that I'm not tall enough to see this.
Oh, that's so annoying.
What if I...
Hey!
Skills to pay the bills.
And then we do this.
I kind of like the stone here on the side.
There's this here.
Oh, I forgot I double jump.
I need to keep remembering that.
Jesus.
Okay, here's a question.
Can I remove...
I...
Let's say I have this in my hand.
Is there a way for me to...
Oops.
I want to remove this.
Wait.
I don't know.
Okay, platform.
It's time for platform.
Oh, no, wait.
This is the difficult part.
Let's see here.
We need wall first.
Otherwise, this won't work.
I don't have any more.
Wall.
Oh, do I need the bench for that?
Wait, whoa!
Oh!
Hello?
Leave him alone.
Where'd you come from?
Dang.
Okay, Hano is already taking...
sitting down in there.
I need to make wall.
All wall.
Wait, I can make different types of wall.
Palm wood wall?
Requires...
Oh, I have one.
Boo.
Delete it.
Just make normal-ass wall.
That's a good start.
Okay, let's get up here.
Man, there's something about just building things in these games.
Like, similar to Minecraft.
You know, it's just relaxing.
Planning out the house.
It feels good.
Feels real nice.
Okay.
And the way I do this now...
I need to make more platforms.
Platforms here.
You feel an evil presence watching you.
I don't think I like that.
In fact, I think I hate that.
What's coming now?
Are we about to be invaded again?
Let's just close everything off, just in case.
Whoops.
Wait, that wasn't...
How did I just jump that high?
Oh, okay.
Put torch here.
Let's go.
Here.
And then here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is it.
There.
Very nice.
And then...
I gotta remove up here.
There.
Oh, I'm getting so good at this.
Very nice.
I guess I'll...
Let's put doors in between.
Let's make like double rooms like this.
Romeo the traveling merchant has departed.
That is sad, isn't it?
Look at that door.
Beautiful.
Make a door here.
Oh, we need to...
First of all...
Oh, hell no.
Oh, no.
What the fuck is this?
Oh, I don't have my...
Bro, I'm dying.
Where's my...
Oh, my God.
Where's my healing items?
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh, get in here.
It's totally unfair that you can go through walls.
I...
Where are my healing items?
I don't think I have any healing items on me.
Fuck.
I couldn't heal.
Oliver was spontaneously lobotomized by something.
Cthulhu.
Shit.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I have no...
I was not ready for that shit.
Also, what is the...
It's V.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
God damn it.
Okay.
I guess that was the evil presence.
Very, very evil.
And now it's gone.
Okay.
Weird.
I don't understand anything.
But I don't care.
I will just happily keep building.
It won't dissuade me.
You can tell me that much.
Does that look nice?
Put that there instead.
I don't know.
I like...
I'm like torn there.
Anyway, I need to get some healing stuff.
That's all I have.
Wait, I could make an oven, couldn't I?
I need to figure out how to make some food.
It's very, very...
Oh no, Joe!
Joe.
When is he coming back?
Oh no.
Make doors.
Three of these.
There.
And then we're going to have a door up here as well.
Oh yeah, look, this house is going to be insane.
Nope, no, no, no.
There.
And then...
Sure.
That looks decent.
Except...
Wait, how does that actually work?
Am I...
Am I using my pickaxe while I do this?
That is a little confusing to me.
I wasn't holding the pickaxe, but I was sort of using the pickaxe.
Nice.
Good.
Okay, we're getting somewhere here.
Just use this.
I also want more fancy lights and not these stupid ass torches.
Now look at this stuff.
This is nice.
Uh, we need...
To delete that.
And acorns, gel.
You know what?
Let's put the campfire outside.
Because that will give me a regen.
Look, live regen is slightly increased.
I need to get my house in order.
So this part down here, I'm going to actually remove this.
This is going to be one big room with all these different tools.
This is the crafting area.
So I'm going to take this thing up here and bring it down.
Heavy workbench.
You get to be right there.
And then there's other things I want to do.
We should have a kitchen.
Oh, Joe is not here!
Um, what could I need to make an oven?
Let's see.
Let's try clay, actually.
Clay and mud?
Stuff like that.
Lead, uh...
Let's try lead bars.
Tungsten.
Let's just go with that for now.
Oh yeah, here we go.
Uh, what can we make?
Okay, let's just go with that for now.
Glass kiln already did that.
Cooking pot?
Wait, does this serve a function or not?
It doesn't say anything like, uh, crafting related.
Empty buckets.
Any iron bar and any wood?
Let's make it...
I can put it on top of this, actually.
That's actually kind of neat.
I can...
Ooh!
Wait, I can sort of place it anywhere?
Oh, wait, I can't.
Okay.
But I can place it here.
No, I can't.
Oh, it needs to be there, I guess.
That's not gonna allow me to do anything special, is it?
Huh.
And I need to get on making actual healing potions.
You know what?
Let's make a reinforced fishing pole and throw out this bullshit.
We don't want that.
And let's also...
Ooh, trap doors?
Fence!
That's what I wanted to do.
Let's make some fence.
Let's see how that works.
Delete it.
Oh no.
Okay.
So I think the hammer is meant to destroy background.
Items.
That's pretty much what that is.
I wonder if this will prevent enemies from traversing this here.
I'm gonna try something.
Oh, wait, I ran out.
Can I make more here?
No.
Oh, man.
Also, maybe I shouldn't make it that high.
Maybe one is enough.
I'm gonna test here.
And that one.
Thank you.
Make more.
Fence.
93.
Actually, let's leave this here for now.
I just want to see if there's monsters coming.
Let's see if it works.
I'm gonna put some on the other side as well.
Just to experiment here.
And let me also fill up this hole.
Because it's ugly.
Look at that.
Nice.
Okay.
Things are starting to come together here.
Take this one and put it down here.
Put it like...
Man, okay.
It's actually kind of weird and annoying that everything is in 2D.
So it's hard to figure out where to place things.
You need a lot of room for this stuff.
Let's just do that for now.
Not that pretty, I know.
And it will be changed.
We need one room just with chests.
And here's what I'm thinking.
Maybe we can make something like this.
Check this out.
Wait.
I have a great idea here.
What's the lowest I can...
Okay, that's the lowest.
This is how we're gonna effectively utilize the space.
I need to make more chests.
Do we want that to be the chest room though?
Hmm.
Yeah, why not?
We started here so may as well continue, right?
Let's see.
Chest.
Now can I do this?
Oh, look at that!
See, that's what I'm talking about!
This is effective use of space.
Uh, I need to do some more of that stuff.
So... can I maybe...
Do something similar with the crafting?
But these things should be on the ground though.
Right?
I like this music.
This is very uh...
Uplifting.
I can make vases and a clay pot.
Gross plants!
Really?
Hell, let's try that.
Um, let me actually...
Oh my god, I can put them...
Q, you can use this to make shelves.
Like, wait a minute.
Let's do that.
There.
Do we need to put a flower in it?
Okay, that's a tree.
You don't want to grow a tree in here.
I guess you could if you wanted.
But that's not really what I'm looking for.
Let's actually sell this stuff.
Vanity items.
I feel like stuff like this can go to hell.
No.
Crimson block?
Bowls?
You know, the bowl is kind of interesting.
Because that will allow me to make some food.
Fruit salad, remember?
But I needed apple for that.
How do I get apple?
From an apple tree.
How do I get an apple tree?
See, that's the question.
I guess you plant an apple,
but you need an apple to begin with to do that.
Um...
Is there a way to sort this list
somehow?
Maybe not.
Let's just check here
if there's anything that will craft.
Furnace, smelting ore.
This is just life regen.
Boulder can be placed.
Slime is falling f-
Heck no.
Heck no, dude.
None on my watch.
Oh, that's a one-shot.
Oh.
We're under attack, people!
Okay, the fence is not working, it seems.
They don't give a shit about the fence.
I think it's cosmetic.
But maybe it will prevent spawning.
That's my big hope here.
Bro.
There we go.
I think these slimes are gonna keep falling for a while.
I should close the doors.
They shouldn't be able to come in, right?
Okay, this guy's in somehow.
Close the doors.
Oh, ah, it's open over here.
I see.
Okay, nice.
Close, close.
Bro.
Get out of here.
Do we have a door?
I do.
Oh, but I don't have a-
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh my god.
Am I dying here?
Quick.
Still hold where you at.
And then door.
Nice.
There it is.
House is now secure.
And now we can relax.
Beautiful.
I don't even need to heal because we have the campfire there.
It's so lovely.
Now, whoops.
Catlin, the nurse has arrived.
What?
Excuse me?
The nurse.
See, that sounds nice.
I feel like I need a nurse.
I've been needing a nurse for a while now.
Let's make some room here for her.
Catlin, just let me deal with this.
Get inside, get to safety.
So, Catlin is nice and all, but what about Joe?
Have you seen that old man pacing around the dungeon?
He looks troubled.
Huh?
No, I have not.
Is there an old man in the dungeon?
Which dungeon?
Uh, happiness.
These things are great.
Loving the personal space.
I'm glad you're happy.
Uh, hmm.
Oh god.
Come on, get out of there.
I love that sound effect.
I'm actually not taking that much damage.
All right, stop opening the doors, people.
The slimes are gonna come inside.
Don't do it.
Uh, now regarding food.
What do we have that can probably be cooked here?
Mushrooms.
Uh, grass.
I don't want to eat any of this.
I want to eat these squirrels.
Cactus, maybe.
Wait, water leaf seeds.
Speaking of seeds.
Can I do farming at all in this game?
Is that actually a thing?
Oh, look.
Flower has grown from the flower pot.
Nice.
No.
Okay.
Man, why do I look like a future soldier?
I feel like my armor makes me look like some kind of starship trooper.
God, it's so satisfying to just hit multiple enemies.
It feels good, man.
Also, I'm very protected.
Look, I take almost no damage from these guys.
They're just pushing me around.
It doesn't even matter.
I shouldn't even fight them.
Just leave them be.
Um, I'm getting a little lost here on...
How to make some proper food?
I really am.
Um...
Right, I wanted to try and plant things.
That's what I was doing.
These things are annoying as hell.
Let's see.
Okay, I can't just put them on the ground.
Looks like I do need some kind of grow bed or something.
Okay.
Uh, so what do I want to do with the rest of these rooms?
I guess I could prepare rooms.
I don't really know what to do with these rooms right now.
We have the crafting down here.
We have...
I feel like I kind of want to evict Hanno.
This is going to be my stuff.
You know, I don't want Hanno here.
Hanno?
You're annoying me.
Let me make a...
Where's it?
A chair?
Make two of these.
Make some tables.
Make a couple chests, I guess.
And also...
Just some random shit, really.
Uh, doors are fine.
Wait, where did the barrel go?
Couldn't I make a barrel or something?
Oh, wait, wait, here it is.
Where?
Trap door.
Is it over here?
There, crate!
What?
Allows only liquids through.
Can we toggle it open or closed?
Oh, it's a crate!
I thought it was a crate!
I have been bamboozled!
Motherfucker!
Let's have a trash can as well, because why not?
We're gonna make it very homey.
And what else can I make?
That's... that's it for now.
Um, let's put the trash can...
Let's put it right here.
No, that's a horrible place for a trash can!
Uh, uh, I don't know, I don't know, actually up here is...
I kind of regret making the... you know what, this can go over here.
Trash can for the people.
There you go, have fun.
Okay, and then let's put a table right there.
Let's put a chair.
How do I rotate the chairs?
Oops.
Oh, that works.
Oh, wait, I think I'm just... ah, okay, it's depending on how you are faced.
I get that now.
Okay, let's put a table.
Let's make it not so symmetric.
Or not so, uh, you know what I mean.
Something like that, you know, it keeps it a little, um, randomized here.
So, in fact, put this... what's... Dylan, the guide has arrived!
Dude, all the people are coming now.
It's probably because we defeated all those enemies and I know we are good for protection now.
Put some more chests, put them up here.
Um, full fill this, like that.
There, there, oh my god, I'm loving how this looks already.
That's great.
Look at all the slimes!
Okay, slimes, it's time.
You... oh!
Dylan!
Okay, I'm coming Dylan!
Rain on these fools.
There we go.
Royal entrance, how about that Dylan?
You like it?
Okay Dylan, thank god you're here.
Um, do-do-do-do-do, tell me about the plate again.
Oh, full.
Fruit salad, right.
Any fruit.
Let me see here again.
Okay, oh my god, here we go.
This is the furniture I was looking for.
Target, oh wow.
Display hats, oh my god.
Keg, use for brewing ale?
Bro!
I love it!
Sawmill, and yes!
Wait, I can't make it.
Yes, I can.
Iron bar, chains and wood.
Lovely.
Um, oops.
I can-I can iron...
chains.
I need chains.
Where's the chains?
Be in here.
There.
And wood I have.
Let's see.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Sawmill!
Fuck yeah, man.
Let's, uh, remove this thing right here first.
Don't care about the cooking pot right now.
Why can't I put this here?
Something on the floor?
What's that?
Oh, a pressure plate.
Right.
I forgot about that.
Also, I just realized this is dirt.
That ain't good.
Let's put some proper flooring.
Also, there's a party in the top room here.
Look at the slimes.
Nice.
Okay.
Um, what was I doing?
Right, I was placing this thing.
There.
What can I make?
Picnic table sword rack.
Oh my, oh my, oh my.
Nice.
The slimes have finally stopped falling from the sky.
Carpentry rack.
Dude, this is awesome.
You know what?
We don't need to have a...
We don't need to have this here.
We don't need to be able to go up everywhere.
This is not going to be a place to go up.
I have decided so.
We don't have enough room.
Nice.
Okay.
Make it real nice now.
Look at that.
What else can we do here?
Hat rack.
Yes, because we have a hat.
Let's put that somewhere.
Maybe we can put it here.
Maybe over here.
Oh god.
We got a slime situation.
Look at the carnage here.
Lovely.
Hat rack.
Goes here.
Somewhere.
Remove the stupid trash can.
I hate it.
There we go.
Now I have a hat.
I had a vanity item.
Didn't I?
It's not in...
Wait, dirt wall?
No.
I don't want that.
That's bad.
Oh wait, I already had tables and stuff.
Ha.
Flare gun.
There it is.
Peddler's hat.
That goes on the hat rack.
Wait, what?
Wait, how did this?
Oh, I see, I see.
Uh...
Hey!
Look at that!
Lovely.
And then...
Okay, you know what?
These slimes are pissing me off.
It's time to die.
Shit.
Just standing here is actually insane.
This platform situation.
Very nice.
Nice.
Okay.
Dylan!
You're the new Joe.
But you shall be called Dylan.
Because that's your name.
What else can you tell me?
You should stay indoors at night.
It's very dangerous to be wandering around in the dark.
It's also dangerous to have a hole in the ceiling.
So let's fix that.
That's how all the slimes got in in the first place.
Okay, Dylan.
I want you to take this wood.
Ah, shit.
Crafting.
Can I shift click this?
I can.
Okay!
What else can we make of nice things here?
Anything with utilization?
Advanced wood crafting?
Uh...
Cake.
I kind of want to make a cake.
Oh.
Wait.
Okay, I can make that.
Fireplace.
Cake, what's this?
What?
That's not something I want to do.
I don't want to summon a goblin army.
Heavy workbench, we have that.
Gold hammer?
Coffin mine cart?
I don't know if I like that.
This requires iron bars and any wood.
Okay, a bit of wood.
Let's see if we can sleep in this game and skip the night.
What does it require?
Silk.
How the fuck do we make that?
Oh, probably from this over here.
The loom.
No, wait.
The loom only makes fabrics out of stuff like silk, doesn't it?
It.
Hano, what do you sell?
Divat.
I don't want to be able to craft dies.
Not right now, at least.
Okay, ten is boring.
Cooking pot?
Brown pressure plate can be used to do a variety of things.
Right, rope coil.
Thompson bullet.
Man, how do I make fucking bullets?
Nothing here.
Wait, what?
Oh, I can turn them into different acorns.
Okay.
Clay block.
Wait, I think this may be it.
Wandering Jingaza?
Your most loyal travel companion.
The glowing orb is soft and welcoming.
Tea pot.
Clay pot, yeah.
Fuck me, dude.
I have no idea what to do here.
Wait.
What is this?
I can make all kinds of weird items out of dirt.
Wait.
Oh, it killed an owl, I see.
Let's actually deploy a certain someone.
Oh, I don't even have that on me.
Let's go to the storage room.
Just keep it on me.
All right, Abigail, go fuck this guy up, will ya?
Go!
He's down there.
Yes.
Are they scared of it?
Oh no, it's because it's becoming morning.
Okay.
Anyway, I wanted to try and craft a bed, but I needed silk.
That's a bit trouble.
How the fuck do you make silk?
Hmm.
Man, I wish I had real-life knowledge right now of how things are made
so I can have an idea of where to go.
I don't, I know surprisingly little about practical stuff.
If we were in the apocalypse, I would die within a week.
That's guaranteed.
I can tell you that much.
Huh?
What's that?
We have a duck somewhere here.
Bluejay?
Hold on.
Who's saying that?
It's over here.
Are you- are you a duck?
I'm confused.
Okay.
Okay, let's actually try and go fishing.
I see water right here, and I know there's water to the east, and it's now day, finally.
So, let's frickin' do it.
First, bam, everything in.
And then we're gonna look at Michelinius.
We're gonna grab the organics, grab this, that, and that.
Let's frickin' go.
We have it on us.
Equip it there.
Let's try.
I'm first gonna try here.
Do I have to apply the bait somehow?
No, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Consumable.
Wait, I think I did it.
Oh, hey, look!
There's a little beetle on my cursor now.
Requires bait to cashfish.
Hmm.
Let me go try to the sea.
Or at least that was a big pond over here.
Also, the dock is definitely to the left somewhere.
Oh, it's hot now.
I actually kind of like this area.
I like the colors of it.
Let's try this.
Let me think.
Yeah, a flounder!
I don't even know what that is, but I'll take it.
English is not my first language.
I don't know what the fuck a flounder is, but I'll take it.
Looks like a fish to me, and that's all I need to know.
Wait, what?
Haley, the zoologist has arrived!
Man, the fishing is faster.
Old shoe.
Come on.
Rock lobster.
But it wasn't a rock.
Dude, this is nice.
I like this.
I like this a lot.
I hear enemy sounds.
Wait, do I need to throw it further?
Come on.
Maybe I need to...
Maybe I fished the entirety of this pond.
Uh oh.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh, don't you disturb my fishing!
Let's try again.
Man, what the...
Are you kidding me?
Leave me alone!
Maybe there is only a certain amount of fish in this.
Bomb fish?
A small explosion that will...
Beautiful.
I love it.
A tin can.
I just can't wait to get home and try and see if I can cook this fish into some delectable meal.
I just want a nice culinary experience.
I just want to enjoy a Chinese succulent meal.
Get your hands off me!
Oh no.
Come on, Abigail.
Get him.
Nice.
Good job.
He's dragonflies here.
I kind of want to...
Catch them with my net.
I really like the haze effect.
So many old shoes!
Who is throwing shoes here?
Galleous!
He's back!
But I still don't have any money.
I have six gold coins.
That's not a lot.
Okay, maybe it does just take a while.
Maybe you can't run out of fish.
Maybe I was just being a bit impatient.
Flounder.
Okay, I want to go try and see if I can cook some of this stuff.
Hold on.
How'd they see me?
I come from water.
Okay, be quiet.
Be quiet.
Let them come close.
Come on.
Navy seal.
Aw, fuck.
I don't know what I just did there.
I'm trying to fish this bird.
And why do the birds have currency?
Well, that's a real question, isn't it?
I should use this.
Wait, this doesn't hang onto trees?
Ha!
All right.
Fine.
Oh my god, look at all the people!
What?
Is this a human or not?
I don't understand what's going on here.
I have no idea how I got here, but it's mega rad.
Sure, Haley.
Who are you?
What do you sell?
Guide to critter companionship.
Prevent you from hurting hurt.
I thought it said hurling.
Prevent you from hurling critters.
I'm hurting critters while in the inventory.
That's actually kind of cool.
Squirrel hook.
Grab on to trees like a real squirrel.
How fitting is that that I find this right after I just said that?
A cat license?
Oh my god.
Kites can be flown on windy days?
Lizard ears?
What the fuck?
I mean, I have money.
I could, I could, you know, purchase a cat license.
Is that really what I want to spend my hard-earned gold on, though?
I'm not sure about that.
Dylan, see you around, man.
Now, can I make some delicious fish somewhere?
Maybe I need a campfire for that, actually.
Let me go next to a campfire.
I mean, it's a material.
I, oh, wait, wait, wait, we got to talk to Dylan about this.
Dylan, look at what I caught.
Shashimi.
It's not food, though.
It's like a buff, though.
So in order to do this, I guess I need some kind of a...
Oh, I have not noticed this until now.
It actually says what you need.
God damn, dude.
No fucking way.
Where is it?
Shashimi.
Yeah.
Okay, now we're talking.
Hey, Dylan, check out what I caught.
It's a rock lobster.
Lobster tail.
Delicious with a bit of butter.
Everything is delicious with a bit of butter.
Oh, I have to go down here, though.
Oh, wait, did I not check?
What kind of, what I needed for that?
Shit.
Do, do, do, do, do, do.
Talk to him, crafting, click on this.
Cooking pot.
Fantastic.
Look what I have.
Notice this as well.
This cooking pot item right there does not actually have a description that says
can be used to craft something.
So this just opened a whole new array of abilities.
Now I know I can use items, probably these as well up here.
God damn.
Get rid of this wood platform.
We are going to place a sashimi on it.
Whoops, I ate it.
Okay, that's fine.
Let's place a bowl on it because it looks nice.
And next to that, ladybug.
That's the name for those.
Right.
Hey Dylan, what do you think of this?
That one?
Oh, you don't like that, you don't like that.
What about the old shoe?
Nothing.
But now I kind of want to check everything again because...
You know, this is a platform.
Hold on, let's see.
What was I confused about earlier?
I don't remember what I was confused about.
Wouldn't sink.
Piano?
The bit requires sawmill.
Okay, but we need silk.
Right, we don't have that.
Target dummy.
Weapon rag.
Item frame.
Oh, and a barrel.
Marshmallow on a stick?
Nice.
Living wood wall.
Wouldn't yoyo.
It's so hard to decide what to make.
I want to make everything.
Like, if I make a bookcase, maybe I can get something out of that.
Seamore.
I want to sell some things, actually.
Sell this stuff, sell this one as well.
Do you like the sh- oh, I can sell this for a lot of money.
This would be a nice way to make some dough in this game, sell it.
You can have this.
Actually, hold on a second.
Can I?
I want to hang an old shoe on this!
I can't.
Oh, man.
That's so sad, though.
Wait, what's this?
Tin can.
No value.
Gallies is gone again.
Hold on, I wanted to place the cooking pot.
Cooking pot goes here.
And then we're gonna craft lobster tails.
Nice.
Increases live regeneration.
See, this is nice to have in a dungeon.
In the green slime banner.
I should have put this down when I fought the green slimes.
Actually, just- it's only green slimes.
It's not any slime, it's just a green slime.
Put it in there for now.
Seaweed.
Can I not make some kind of food out of that?
Oh, wait, you're not Dylan.
Dylan, where are you at?
Dylan?
Hold on a sec.
Oh, wait, he's here.
Oh, he was blocking him, I think.
Wait, did I- am I able to ask for something else?
Help.
If you had a gun, I bet an arms dealer might show up to sell you some ammo.
I see.
Hold on.
But I have a gun.
Let me equip it, actually.
Just have it equipped.
Maybe an arms dealer would show up then.
But here's my question.
Is he only gonna show up if I make room for it?
Because as soon as I made these rooms, everyone was flocking here.
So I think I need to make more rooms first, otherwise they're not gonna show up.
Actually, when you think about it, that makes total sense.
I could- I should expand this house right here.
Or connect them here.
Wouldn't that be kind of cool?
I'm gonna do that.
We're expanding, boys.
Give me the wall.
Make it like that.
Whoops.
No!
Don't drop it!
Dummy.
Oh my god, I'm terrible.
And then, we need this.
This way we're also protected down here when we transfer from house to house, right?
I- actually, I like how this looks.
This makes- this is pleasing to my eye.
Oh look, the chests light up when you get close to them.
Probably indicating that you can transfer things to them automatically.
Or it means I can right click it from here.
Yeah, that's probably what that means, actually.
Never mind.
Don't drop the thingy.
Nice.
Uh, this I don't like.
I'm gonna remove this right here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Keep doing the thing.
This is gonna look a little weird, but that's okay.
Oh no!
Okay, that's fine.
Yeah, we don't- we can expand this down here as well, do you like that?
Like, why wouldn't- why wouldn't we do this?
Right.
This is all gonna be connected.
It's gonna be one big nice family.
Kind of looks nice, doesn't it?
I like it.
And maybe I don't like the, uh, the stone in the middle of the house, actually.
Maybe I'll do something like this instead.
Or even better.
We don't need a door down here now.
There.
Why- why does this look like it's destroyed?
Maybe it was a little bit there.
Better.
And then we need to clear this flooring.
I kind of wish I could...
Hmm.
Oh, but I can.
Oh, but I can!
Wait a sec.
Put it there.
And then use...
Uh, where is it?
This one.
Finish this like that.
And then remove that one.
Oh, this is gonna look so good!
Just watch.
Like that.
And then, uh, we're gonna make the stairs.
Yep, yep, yep.
Look!
At that!
Isn't that fantastic.
And the door is also kind of not needed, I guess?
Or maybe it is, I don't know.
Maybe, actually, maybe if you don't have a door, it's not gonna
count as separating the rooms properly.
You know?
So, I think the door is necessary.
Otherwise, this will be, uh, part of...
What's her name?
Catlin's house, right?
This right here.
But this is my workshop.
This is where I hang out.
And nobody's allowed in here.
Seaweed goes in the trash.
Plate goes in trash.
Actually, plate goes out of trash.
And it goes on this.
Actually, no.
You know what?
Dylan, you get to have a plate.
There you go.
You like it?
Does that mean you don't like it?
Help!
You should prove yourself by defeating a strong monster.
That will get the attention of a dryad.
Yeah, you said that once and I'm not quite sure what the
fuck you're talking about.
But I will.
I just need to get stronger first.
And once I'm at a stylist,
she went off adventuring on the ground.
And that was the last I saw of her.
Wonder what became of her.
Okay, the game is...
Motherfucker killing the...
The game is heavily implying that I can rescue NPCs in the dungeon.
It's been set twice now.
So I need to go down into a dungeon and find someone to rescue.
Question is, what counts as the dungeon?
Right?
Like, there's so many caves.
What exactly...
Where do they want me to go?
Precisely here.
Can you give me some directions at least?
Click on this button.
Ores and ores.
Doors go in.
And the ores go in.
This dart trap.
Put it in miscellaneous for now.
This chain goes in here.
This...
Wait, water leaf seeds.
Maybe they need water.
And you know what?
I can make something incredible.
But not right now, because I don't have the fucking thing I just threw away.
Need lead.
And then...
Let's see here.
Empty bucket!
Wait, I can equip it?
Well, uh...
Not quite what I want to do.
But sure.
I'm gonna find some water.
It's door time!
Walking through all the doors.
I actually fucking love that the door automatically opens.
In Minecraft, you had to right-click every time.
I mean, it's a little easy in a 3D game, but you know.
Uh...
Wait.
What was I doing?
Right, getting water.
Here's my plant.
I'm gonna get water.
And see if I can plant that water seed in the water.
Let me grab the purest of all the water.
Yeah!
So what happens if I...
Oh, right.
See, that makes sense!
Not unlike some other game!
You put it and then it's just a fucking waterfall.
Hey!
Stop your shenanigans!
So the question is, if I make a little...
Let's see here.
What does this actually say?
It contains a small amount.
It can be poured out right.
Actually, let me try something first.
Since I'm here.
Wait.
No.
Okay, that's not working.
Ah, wait, I...
I was about to say, I can't place this.
Because it's going to pour it.
It's not going to place the item.
Fuck, never mind.
Um, here's the thing I want to try.
Wait.
Oh, oh, look at this!
The smart cursor!
Ah, ha!
That is revealing that.
That's great.
Okay.
That's very nice to know.
Right.
Now the lens.
Uh, Dylan, you need to tell me about the lens again.
I forgot what you said.
Goggles.
Isn't this the thing that I fought?
Summons the twins.
Summons twins to fight for you.
What?
Can I make this?
I require all kinds of shit for that.
Oh, no, no, no, that's not happening.
Nope.
That is not happening.
Unfortunately.
Anyway, holy shit!
Oh my god!
Fuck!
I've been playing for four and a half hours.
Jesus Christ.
I need to stop.
Immediately.
Wow.
Damn.
Man, time is flying when you play this game.
Hold on.
All right, people!
Let me open chat.
Let me see here.
Yeah, chat is coming in.
I see the chat.
There it is.
Okay, uh, I actually got to go immediately.
Um, I just want to say, uh,
Shadow Six.
Hi, Oliver.
Love you, bitch.
Just finished Outer Wiles.
And now watching your Minecraft stuff.
Keep doing what you do, bro.
Grade A content.
Thank you so much, Shadow Six.
I don't know if you're still here, but if you are,
I appreciate it.
And I'm glad you're enjoying the content.
Rain Harper has become a potato.
Let's welcome him to the, to the pantry.
Thanks for joining Rain Harper.
I haven't seen you before.
Maybe I have.
I don't remember then.
Nice to have you.
I need to get out of here because
I need to go to work early tomorrow.
And it's kind of late already for me.
So, yeah.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could stay and chat,
but I was completely enveloped by the game once again.
You know, it is what it is.
The stream chat is what's being printed.
Yes, exactly.
You got it, man.
Exactement.
Okay, guys, thanks for watching.
There's so many people watching this.
It's insane.
There's so many who enjoys Terraria, I guess.
I guess it's a very popular game.
Thanks for checking it out.
Check out the Discord if you haven't joined yet.
It's a cool place with cool people,
and you're not going to regret it.
And if you are, that's fine too.
Anyway, thanks for watching.
I will see you guys in the next stream or video.
Have a good one.
Adios.